[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Comment: Processed by 繁化姬 dict-001ce893-r978 @ 2021/09/23 03:08:38 | https://zhconvert.org
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Active Line: 6

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H00C14F0D,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: OPJP,A-OTF Kakushin Gyousho Std M,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H00262628,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: OPCN,方正正中黑_GBK,80,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H004C04CA,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,35,1
Style: EDJP,Source Han Serif CN,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: EDCN,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,2,15,15,15,1
Style: Tips,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H005A5A61,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0.5,2,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,@腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,130,&H005E03DD,&H000B24FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,7,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Next,腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,90,&H001004A4,&H000B24FF,&H00000000,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0,8,10,10,25,1
Style: Song1,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: Song2,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: Song3,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.99,0:00:34.11,OPCN,,0,0,0,,就算一无所有也还有明天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.11,0:00:35.96,OPCN,,0,0,0,,跌落谷底 回归原点
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.96,0:00:36.94,OPCN,,0,0,0,,这也是天性使然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.54,0:00:39.87,OPCN,,0,0,0,,哪怕燃烧殆尽也要实现目标
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.87,0:00:42.15,OPCN,,0,0,0,,反击时刻现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.35,0:00:47.25,OPCN,,0,0,0,,无礼禁断
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.86,0:00:52.72,OPCN,,0,0,0,,彻头彻尾成就
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.72,0:00:55.56,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有人提出了挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.56,0:00:57.38,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 毅然奋起
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.38,0:01:02.27,OPCN,,0,0,0,,你想要贯彻什么？
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.75,0:01:06.51,OPCN,,0,0,0,,带着蜡烛的灯火
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.51,0:01:08.40,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 孤注一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.40,0:01:13.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,向前进 然后终将燃烧殆尽
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.80,0:01:17.28,OPCN,,0,0,0,,会是蝼蚁或亡者
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.28,0:01:20.22,OPCN,,0,0,0,,还是闪烁的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.22,0:01:23.41,OPCN,,0,0,0,,赌上仅有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.42,0:01:27.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,试图奋力挣扎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.78,0:01:31.86,OPCN,,0,0,0,,将命运吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.86,0:01:34.74,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如吞噬生命的实感般疾驰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.74,0:01:37.53,OPCN,,0,0,0,,不论他人如何掠夺 (奔跑吧)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.53,0:01:38.84,OPCN,,0,0,0,,从今以后 (不需要)
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.84,0:01:40.88,OPCN,,0,0,0,,都再也不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.88,0:01:42.89,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如泉水涌出般
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.89,0:01:45.61,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有朝一日一起放声哭泣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.61,0:01:47.40,OPCN,,0,0,0,,燃起胧月篝火
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.41,0:01:50.09,OPCN,,0,0,0,,谁要去指望什么来生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.09,0:01:53.81,OPCN,,0,0,0,,顺从内心重新脱胎换骨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.81,0:01:55.85,OPCN,,0,0,0,,直到永远
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.85,0:01:59.01,OPCN,,0,0,0,,SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----EDCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.57,0:22:04.99,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}面对那如梦似幻的无尽日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.99,0:22:12.99,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}一起踏出找寻明日的旅程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.64,0:22:24.79,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}回忆中的街道 改变了的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.24,0:22:31.44,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}像个迷路的孩子般徘徊其中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.88,0:22:40.14,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}至少拥抱心胸的伤口向前进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.15,0:22:48.79,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}因为再也没有回头的理由了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.22,0:22:52.32,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}将梦想掌握手中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.32,0:22:58.56,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}漫步于没有归处的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.56,0:23:05.74,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}为肯定这将是场无可取代的旅程前进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.74,0:23:12.12,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}就算像发梦般遗忘了也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.12,0:23:14.31,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}我们不会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.31,0:23:17.30,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}哪怕夕阳西沉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.30,0:23:21.57,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}也要踏出步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Song 1-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.93,0:00:51.86,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord16\3c&H000000\shad0}丧尸们将会如何复仇呢 佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.93,0:00:51.86,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord10\shad0}丧尸们将会如何复仇呢 佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.04,0:02:02.77,Tips,,0,0,0,,ARPINO演唱会结束三周后
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.69,0:08:03.08,Tips,,0,0,0,,演出前一天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.87,0:08:45.28,Tips,,0,0,0,,演出当天
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:03.96,Tips,,0,0,0,,(不准碰！幸太郎的存钱筒)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.94,0:23:40.01,Next,,0,0,0,,第十一话 比方说只要有你在·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Main-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.61,0:00:02.61,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么要我当偶像？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.61,0:00:05.24,Default,,0,0,0,,就取名为"丧尸乐园计划"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.24,0:00:06.74,Default,,0,0,0,,靠当地偶像振兴乡里？
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.74,0:00:08.49,Default,,0,0,0,,这是重获新生的莉莉和大家的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.49,0:00:09.66,Default,,0,0,0,,糟糕糟糕糟糕糟糕糟糕　　怎么办怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.66,0:00:11.37,Default,,0,0,0,,不用担心 我会支援你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.37,0:00:12.43,Default,,0,0,0,,只要我够幸运就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.43,0:00:13.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我宁可和樱一起站上舞台然后失败
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.77,0:00:16.29,Default,,0,0,0,,今后我也会以法兰秀秀一员的身份
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.29,0:00:18.67,Default,,0,0,0,,这计划打从一开始就太强人所难了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.67,0:00:21.79,Default,,0,0,0,,这项计划的时间是有限的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.79,0:00:23.59,Default,,0,0,0,,绝对不会错的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.59,0:00:25.26,Default,,0,0,0,,她们都已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.26,0:00:28.09,Default,,0,0,0,,再不然就是起死回生的丧尸了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.39,0:02:06.94,Default,,0,0,0,,这篇报道写得不错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.94,0:02:08.66,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀果然
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.66,0:02:11.13,Default,,0,0,0,,还是要我们七个人都在才行呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.73,0:02:15.24,Default,,0,0,0,,"演唱会结束后发售了首张专辑"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.24,0:02:16.87,Default,,0,0,0,,"在佐贺偶像界罕见地"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.90,0:02:18.95,Default,,0,0,0,,"获得还过得去的销售成绩"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.95,0:02:21.91,Default,,0,0,0,,要是能写"魔法大热卖"就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.91,0:02:24.40,Default,,0,0,0,,是每次都会为我们写报道的记者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.40,0:02:26.97,Default,,0,0,0,,他有时会写出很一针见血的评论
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.97,0:02:28.34,Default,,0,0,0,,是可以信任的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.34,0:02:29.96,Default,,0,0,0,,要好好珍惜才行
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.80,0:02:33.63,Default,,0,0,0,,我看下次可以直冲一千人了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.63,0:02:36.55,Default,,0,0,0,,要是太得意忘形 小心会失败
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.55,0:02:37.96,Default,,0,0,0,,大家不能太大意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.96,0:02:39.64,Default,,0,0,0,,好好绷紧神经吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.64,0:02:40.47,Default,,0,0,0,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.47,0:02:43.35,Default,,0,0,0,,那为了避免失败 大家先好好绷紧神经
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.35,0:02:45.27,Default,,0,0,0,,以一千人为目标努力吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.28,0:02:49.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我说你们
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.23,0:02:51.52,Default,,0,0,0,,到底想沉醉在ARPINO的成功多久啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.52,0:02:54.82,Default,,0,0,0,,这班烂醉丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.82,0:02:58.03,Default,,0,0,0,,丧尸没那个时间和脑袋 回顾过往的荣耀
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.03,0:02:58.99,Default,,0,0,0,,因为所以
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.99,0:02:59.99,Default,,0,0,0,,看过来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.99,0:03:02.73,Default,,0,0,0,,我们要一鼓作气在车站前不动产体育场
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.73,0:03:06.38,Default,,0,0,0,,简称EFS举行演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.38,0:03:09.46,Default,,0,0,0,,车站前…不动产？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.00,0:03:10.96,Default,,0,0,0,,小爱？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.96,0:03:14.01,Default,,0,0,0,,莉莉从来没听说过这个体育场
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.01,0:03:16.48,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然听上去好像还挺有来头的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:19.80,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我们会用号召一千人的气势应战的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.81,0:03:21.39,Default,,0,0,0,,那个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.39,0:03:23.93,Default,,0,0,0,,听说是下个月要改的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.93,0:03:26.27,Default,,0,0,0,,调查得真清楚
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.27,0:03:28.40,Default,,0,0,0,,之后要改名字？
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.40,0:03:30.19,Default,,0,0,0,,那现在叫什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.30,0:03:33.32,Default,,0,0,0,,"Best Amenity Stadium"
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.31,0:03:35.82,Default,,0,0,0,,鸟栖体育场
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.64,0:03:40.74,Default,,0,0,0,,小爱…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.75,0:03:42.41,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你们 我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.06,0:03:45.25,Default,,0,0,0,,问题是那个地方的大小
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.32,0:03:49.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我记得那里的收容人数…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.25,0:03:50.92,Default,,0,0,0,,约两万五千人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.36,0:03:53.92,Default,,0,0,0,,两万五千人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.92,0:03:55.64,Default,,0,0,0,,那不是ARPINO的五十倍吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.64,0:03:58.22,Default,,0,0,0,,如果把竞技场也算进去就更多了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.99,0:04:00.43,Default,,0,0,0,,根本无法想象
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.43,0:04:02.35,Default,,0,0,0,,这是我们能对付的数量吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.35,0:04:03.64,Default,,0,0,0,,要在那么厉害的地方…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.64,0:04:05.18,Default,,0,0,0,,想也知道不可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.93,0:04:09.02,Default,,0,0,0,,演唱会将在三月八日举行
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.02,0:04:10.48,Default,,0,0,0,,不要说傻话了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.48,0:04:12.98,Default,,0,0,0,,这里不是福冈 是佐贺啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.98,0:04:14.48,Default,,0,0,0,,当时在佐贺的体育场办演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.48,0:04:15.94,Default,,0,0,0,,也是因为是钢铁裙摆才有办法…
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.94,0:04:19.49,Default,,0,0,0,,现在的你们在她们之上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.81,0:04:22.08,Default,,0,0,0,,不然是怎样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.08,0:04:24.63,Default,,0,0,0,,难道你们是想说法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.65,0:04:27.44,Default,,0,0,0,,比不上十年前的钢铁裙摆吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.48,0:04:31.50,Default,,0,0,0,,你们每个人都是当代的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.66,0:04:37.59,Default,,0,0,0,,除了一个人以外全都是传说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.59,0:04:39.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这是看着我讲的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.64,0:04:42.05,Default,,0,0,0,,我为了拯救佐贺所千挑万选
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.05,0:04:43.35,Default,,0,0,0,,重获生命起死回生的你们
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.35,0:04:44.89,Default,,0,0,0,,没什么是不可能的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.89,0:04:48.73,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀的粉丝一定会挤爆站前体育场
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.73,0:04:49.89,Default,,0,0,0,,紧接着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.90,0:04:51.27,Default,,0,0,0,,等会场气氛达到最高点时
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.27,0:04:54.23,Default,,0,0,0,,就在安可时间发表新歌
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.43,0:04:58.32,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.32,0:05:01.41,Default,,0,0,0,,即将要大大大大大爆发啦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.51,0:05:05.19,Default,,0,0,0,,就连我也看得出来
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.21,0:05:08.54,Default,,0,0,0,,太阳眼镜从来没讲过这么乱来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.54,0:05:10.29,Default,,0,0,0,,果然还是太困难了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.29,0:05:12.54,Default,,0,0,0,,照理来说是百分之百不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.54,0:05:14.71,Default,,0,0,0,,这决定实在太跳脱常识了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.71,0:05:15.75,Default,,0,0,0,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.75,0:05:16.71,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.71,0:05:19.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我们早就是超乎常理和常识的存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.30,0:05:20.47,Default,,0,0,0,,说得也是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.47,0:05:23.43,Default,,0,0,0,,如果说幸太郎先生是认真的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.43,0:05:26.39,Default,,0,0,0,,就表示他应该有什么把握吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.39,0:05:28.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你的意思是巽有什么计划吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.90,0:05:34.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我们就试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.59,0:05:38.07,Default,,0,0,0,,你知道你这话是什么意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.07,0:05:39.99,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然不知道能不能成功
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.99,0:05:42.66,Default,,0,0,0,,但既然有能和大家一起唱歌跳舞的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.66,0:05:44.78,Default,,0,0,0,,我就愿意挑战一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.78,0:05:46.16,Default,,0,0,0,,我想要有更多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.16,0:05:47.99,Default,,0,0,0,,和大家一起站上舞台的机会
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.84,0:05:50.19,Default,,0,0,0,,说得好
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.20,0:05:51.16,Default,,0,0,0,,在ARPINO办演唱会时
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.17,0:05:52.75,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然也碰上很多问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.75,0:05:54.28,Default,,0,0,0,,但大家还是想办法克服了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.28,0:05:55.07,Default,,0,0,0,,现在想想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.07,0:05:57.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我们每一次都非常乱来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.25,0:05:59.67,Default,,0,0,0,,反正我们都已经是丧尸了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.67,0:06:02.18,Default,,0,0,0,,事到如今根本就没什么好怕的了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.18,0:06:04.22,Default,,0,0,0,,一听见大家这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.22,0:06:06.93,Default,,0,0,0,,我就开始有种能办到的感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.93,0:06:08.56,Default,,0,0,0,,连我自己都感到不可思议
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:13.69,Default,,0,0,0,,真是一班乐观的傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.69,0:06:15.02,Default,,0,0,0,,既然要做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.02,0:06:17.65,Default,,0,0,0,,就要展现出超越ARPINO时的最高表现
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.65,0:06:19.37,Default,,0,0,0,,如果抱着半桶水的心态
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.37,0:06:21.07,Default,,0,0,0,,一定会以失败收场的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.07,0:06:23.28,Default,,0,0,0,,小爱 拜托你严格训练了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.28,0:06:24.70,Default,,0,0,0,,这还用说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.70,0:06:26.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我会趁这次机会
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.33,0:06:27.52,Default,,0,0,0,,把你们还不行的地方重新锻炼好的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.14,0:06:29.33,Default,,0,0,0,,特别是樱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.90,0:06:31.79,Default,,0,0,0,,不过要温柔一点哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.79,0:06:33.66,Default,,0,0,0,,你在什么说傻话啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.77,0:06:44.93,Default,,0,0,0,,你果然还是很在意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.93,0:06:47.14,Default,,0,0,0,,会在意是当然的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.14,0:06:49.51,Default,,0,0,0,,再怎么说也是我死掉的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.52,0:06:52.27,Default,,0,0,0,,放心吧 反正也不会死第二次了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.27,0:06:54.64,Default,,0,0,0,,在同一个悬崖跳过两次的咲
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.64,0:06:55.81,Default,,0,0,0,,大概也不会懂吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.50,0:07:02.78,Default,,0,0,0,,你那个时候在公园说过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.78,0:07:04.45,Default,,0,0,0,,不管变成丧尸还是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.45,0:07:06.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我都一定要重新站上那个舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.62,0:07:07.87,Default,,0,0,0,,从那里再一次…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.15,0:07:10.62,Default,,0,0,0,,我就来替你实现吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.62,0:07:13.08,Default,,0,0,0,,如果有什么问题我都会罩你的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.08,0:07:14.50,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然我的头衔是总长
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.50,0:07:16.67,Default,,0,0,0,,但内心可是特攻队长啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.67,0:07:19.04,Default,,0,0,0,,应该不是总长 而是队长吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.70,0:07:22.05,Default,,0,0,0,,很恐怖耶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.05,0:07:23.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我到处都找不到你们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.59,0:07:24.80,Default,,0,0,0,,所以才过来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.89,0:07:27.47,Default,,0,0,0,,也不是在谈什么大事啦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.47,0:07:28.43,Default,,0,0,0,,没问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.95,0:07:31.06,Default,,0,0,0,,我也会支援大家的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.06,0:07:34.14,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然偷听人讲话感觉好像不太好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.14,0:07:35.18,Default,,0,0,0,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.19,0:07:37.44,Default,,0,0,0,,那就来办个集会提振一下士气吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.44,0:07:39.56,Default,,0,0,0,,我们又不是暴走族
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.59,0:07:50.91,Default,,0,0,0,,这样不对
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.53,0:07:54.29,Default,,0,0,0,,想也知道不可能啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.50,0:08:00.69,Default,,0,0,0,,不对
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.17,0:08:05.88,Default,,0,0,0,,还真大
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.26,0:08:08.30,Default,,0,0,0,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.85,0:08:11.64,Default,,0,0,0,,之前我因为很怕所以都不敢问
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.64,0:08:14.68,Default,,0,0,0,,请问预售票目前卖出多少张了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.68,0:08:16.23,Default,,0,0,0,,没准备那种东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.09,0:08:18.39,Default,,0,0,0,,这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.40,0:08:20.44,Default,,0,0,0,,只会在当天开放现场售票
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.44,0:08:22.27,Default,,0,0,0,,你到底在想什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.27,0:08:23.39,Default,,0,0,0,,必须借由这次演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.40,0:08:27.03,Default,,0,0,0,,让全世界知道佐贺的法兰秀秀这个存在
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.03,0:08:27.90,Default,,0,0,0,,为了这个目的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.90,0:08:30.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你们在全方面都必须成为传说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.62,0:08:32.70,Default,,0,0,0,,只靠一般的做法是不够的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.81,0:08:36.41,Default,,0,0,0,,回想起你们过去一路上的丰功伟业吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.58,0:08:38.96,Default,,0,0,0,,相信法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.96,0:08:40.88,Default,,0,0,0,,然后相信我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.59,0:08:54.47,Default,,0,0,0,,罚球区就容纳完所有的观众了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.64,0:08:57.14,Default,,0,0,0,,大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.14,0:09:00.36,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢各位今天过来观赏…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.36,0:09:02.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我们是法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.29,0:09:35.26,Default,,0,0,0,,这下要怎么安可…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.26,0:09:37.89,Default,,0,0,0,,未免也太惨了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.88,0:09:40.73,Default,,0,0,0,,这里是地狱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.49,0:10:12.34,Default,,0,0,0,,窝回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.62,0:10:16.18,Default,,0,0,0,,是法兰幼幼耶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.18,0:10:17.30,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰幼幼w
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.31,0:10:19.39,Default,,0,0,0,,幸太郎先生 你一直没回来
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.39,0:10:21.18,Default,,0,0,0,,害我们好担心你　　是 是是是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.18,0:10:24.65,Default,,0,0,0,,幸太郎先生现在回来咯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.38,0:10:29.58,Default,,0,0,0,,你一直喝酒喝到天亮吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.58,0:10:30.78,Default,,0,0,0,,对啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.78,0:10:31.78,Default,,0,0,0,,因为
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.78,0:10:36.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在背了两千万的借款
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.45,0:10:37.74,Default,,0,0,0,,很厉害对不对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.74,0:10:41.08,Default,,0,0,0,,两千万的借款啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.08,0:10:42.41,Default,,0,0,0,,借款
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.41,0:10:44.08,Default,,0,0,0,,两千万元
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.08,0:10:45.12,Default,,0,0,0,,真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.13,0:10:46.29,Default,,0,0,0,,恐怕是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.00,0:10:50.09,Default,,0,0,0,,举行那种大规模演唱会结果却一败涂地
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.09,0:10:51.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是理所当然的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.39,0:10:54.93,Default,,0,0,0,,做什么一脸正经八百的表情啦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.93,0:10:56.34,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀已经完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.34,0:10:57.85,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺也已经完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.85,0:10:59.68,Default,,0,0,0,,全部都完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.40,0:11:01.64,Default,,0,0,0,,完蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.52,0:11:04.02,Default,,0,0,0,,那个臭太阳眼镜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.02,0:11:06.44,Default,,0,0,0,,他已经连续喝酒两个星期了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.44,0:11:09.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我们的食物吃完也已经过七天了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.78,0:11:11.86,Default,,0,0,0,,就算不吃饭也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.86,0:11:13.44,Default,,0,0,0,,因为我们是丧尸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.45,0:11:15.57,Default,,0,0,0,,幸太郎先生现在说不定
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.57,0:11:17.95,Default,,0,0,0,,已经在构想下一次的作战了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.95,0:11:19.03,Default,,0,0,0,,他之前也都是…
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.03,0:11:20.91,Default,,0,0,0,,他根本什么都没在想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.91,0:11:23.33,Default,,0,0,0,,所以现在事情才会变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.33,0:11:25.46,Default,,0,0,0,,你对樱迁怒也无补于事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.46,0:11:27.88,Default,,0,0,0,,生气的人不是只有你而已
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.88,0:11:29.54,Default,,0,0,0,,那你说现在该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.54,0:11:31.92,Default,,0,0,0,,你们两个不要吵了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.92,0:11:32.99,Default,,0,0,0,,就是在这种时候
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.99,0:11:34.59,Default,,0,0,0,,大家才更该团结一致
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.59,0:11:36.43,Default,,0,0,0,,这样一定会有办法解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.43,0:11:38.30,Default,,0,0,0,,就算你要我们团结一致
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.30,0:11:40.55,Default,,0,0,0,,但只有我们的话不只是化妆
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.56,0:11:42.81,Default,,0,0,0,,甚至连外出购物都没办法啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.81,0:11:44.64,Default,,0,0,0,,而且在我们一筹莫展的现在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.64,0:11:47.60,Default,,0,0,0,,两千万的借款也正在持续不断增加
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.60,0:11:48.45,Default,,0,0,0,,现在的状况
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.47,0:11:51.01,Default,,0,0,0,,不是说乐观的话就有办法好转的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.14,0:11:58.45,Default,,0,0,0,,小妙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.45,0:12:01.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你的脸怎么变成这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.85,0:12:17.34,Default,,0,0,0,,这是她一个人买的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.90,0:12:18.80,Default,,0,0,0,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.80,0:12:20.43,Default,,0,0,0,,她找出了巽藏的钱？
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.43,0:12:21.93,Default,,0,0,0,,连化妆也是她自己…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.14,Default,,0,0,0,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.94,0:12:30.44,Default,,0,0,0,,我们大家都错了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.21,0:12:33.07,Default,,0,0,0,,只要有心我们都办得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.07,0:12:34.23,Default,,0,0,0,,就像小妙一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.04,0:12:37.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我们只是连去做的念头都没有而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.61,0:12:40.78,Default,,0,0,0,,丧尸少了巽先生就什么也做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.78,0:12:41.95,Default,,0,0,0,,我们都因为这样而死心
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.95,0:12:43.53,Default,,0,0,0,,放弃了思考
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.36,0:12:45.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我们都在不知不觉中
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.70,0:12:47.87,Default,,0,0,0,,将依靠幸太郎先生视为理所当然
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.87,0:12:48.96,Default,,0,0,0,,没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.96,0:12:50.79,Default,,0,0,0,,现在想想站前体育场的演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.79,0:12:52.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我们也都觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.25,0:12:53.50,Default,,0,0,0,,只要努力去练习
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.50,0:12:55.21,Default,,0,0,0,,他就会替我们解决问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.85,0:12:57.55,Default,,0,0,0,,这样是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.37,0:13:00.97,Default,,0,0,0,,既然都有化妆用品了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.97,0:13:02.47,Default,,0,0,0,,就赶快开始来化吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.47,0:13:04.97,Default,,0,0,0,,那借款要怎么还才好呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.97,0:13:06.02,Default,,0,0,0,,来工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.02,0:13:07.56,Default,,0,0,0,,现在没办法当偶像的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.56,0:13:08.79,Default,,0,0,0,,那在能继续当偶像前
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.79,0:13:10.73,Default,,0,0,0,,大家就先一起想赚钱的办法吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.73,0:13:12.44,Default,,0,0,0,,莉莉也有办法赚钱吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.44,0:13:13.28,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.28,0:13:14.36,Default,,0,0,0,,一起加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.36,0:13:16.48,Default,,0,0,0,,走一步算一步是我的专长
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.48,0:13:18.86,Default,,0,0,0,,今后的事就靠大家一起想吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.86,0:13:20.58,Default,,0,0,0,,不能被过去束缚
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.58,0:13:21.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我们要眼放未来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.39,0:13:27.62,Default,,0,0,0,,是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.62,0:13:29.54,Default,,0,0,0,,到头来我其实还是…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.02,0:13:32.04,Default,,0,0,0,,小爱
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.54,0:13:33.58,Default,,0,0,0,,加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.24,0:13:35.42,Default,,0,0,0,,如果这个都做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.42,0:13:37.00,Default,,0,0,0,,那我们就只是班丧尸了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.72,0:13:38.67,Default,,0,0,0,,加油吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.67,0:13:41.26,Default,,0,0,0,,我们一定要想办法卷土重来
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.81,0:13:58.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我看这应该是死了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.24,0:14:00.74,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么回事 这些全是墨鱼吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.74,0:14:02.91,Default,,0,0,0,,你有碰过这么奇怪的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.38,0:14:04.32,Default,,0,0,0,,他还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.77,0:14:06.12,Default,,0,0,0,,小兄弟 你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.01,0:14:11.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.21,0:14:13.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是被海浪卷走了而已
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.14,0:14:20.13,Default,,0,0,0,,听说就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.13,0:14:21.84,Default,,0,0,0,,很有意思对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.84,0:14:24.05,Default,,0,0,0,,我们去追那个墨鱼男吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.05,0:14:25.85,Default,,0,0,0,,交给你去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.85,0:14:26.80,Default,,0,0,0,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.81,0:14:29.60,Default,,0,0,0,,大古场先生手上的独家真的这么大条吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.60,0:14:32.85,Default,,0,0,0,,东京的出版社八成不会错过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.66,0:14:34.69,Default,,0,0,0,,犬走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.69,0:14:35.77,Default,,0,0,0,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.77,0:14:36.86,Default,,0,0,0,,没办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.86,0:14:39.48,Default,,0,0,0,,那我就一边找墨鱼男一边慢慢等吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.58,0:14:47.57,Default,,0,0,0,,大家早安
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.58,0:14:49.29,Default,,0,0,0,,你是怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.29,0:14:50.16,Default,,0,0,0,,别在意
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.43,0:14:55.21,Default,,0,0,0,,你也说点甚…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.21,0:14:56.21,Default,,0,0,0,,一年前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.08,0:14:58.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我做错了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.34,0:15:01.09,Default,,0,0,0,,去年三月八日
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.09,0:15:03.06,Default,,0,0,0,,在站前体育场强行举办演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.06,0:15:04.55,Default,,0,0,0,,完全是我的不对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.55,0:15:05.76,Default,,0,0,0,,真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.69,0:15:10.35,Default,,0,0,0,,为了弥补这个错误
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.35,0:15:12.06,Default,,0,0,0,,我们要在下个月三月八日
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.06,0:15:14.14,Default,,0,0,0,,于站前体育场举行卷土重来演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.07,0:15:19.98,Default,,0,0,0,,于站前体育场举行卷土重来演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.98,0:15:20.58,Default,,0,0,0,,等…
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.58,0:15:21.57,Default,,0,0,0,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.57,0:15:22.65,Default,,0,0,0,,这次我不会再像之前那样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.65,0:15:25.90,Default,,0,0,0,,因为自恃甚高 而单凭气势贸然行事了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.82,0:15:29.95,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀成功在这短短一年内复活
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.00,0:15:33.20,Default,,0,0,0,,专辑和周边的业绩
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.20,0:15:36.58,Default,,0,0,0,,也像滨野浦跟蕨野的梯田般欣欣向荣
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.17,0:15:38.29,Default,,0,0,0,,而最重要的是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.29,0:15:40.34,Default,,0,0,0,,你们也都成长了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.28,0:15:44.47,Default,,0,0,0,,但即使如此 站前体育场也是个强敌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.47,0:15:45.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我现在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.59,0:15:48.97,Default,,0,0,0,,正在进行各种 卷土重来演唱会的宣传计划
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.49,0:15:50.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我将赌上我的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.99,0:15:52.68,Default,,0,0,0,,竭尽所能去努力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.68,0:15:53.77,Default,,0,0,0,,然后
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.77,0:15:56.56,Default,,0,0,0,,为了让法兰秀秀成为更伟大的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.56,0:15:59.10,Default,,0,0,0,,我要让那次的失败成为成功的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.30,0:16:02.15,Default,,0,0,0,,所以你才会选在三月八日
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.78,0:16:03.78,Default,,0,0,0,,听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.78,0:16:05.69,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在即将开始的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.70,0:16:08.49,Default,,0,0,0,,将成为佐贺史上最伟大的事件
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.49,0:16:10.45,Default,,0,0,0,,永远留在历史之中
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.45,0:16:12.28,Default,,0,0,0,,哪怕佐贺这片土地
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.29,0:16:14.25,Default,,0,0,0,,在残酷的命运尽头
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.25,0:16:16.71,Default,,0,0,0,,被绝望的黑暗吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.71,0:16:21.50,Default,,0,0,0,,你们都将成为在那里闪耀光辉的存在
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.20,0:16:23.42,Default,,0,0,0,,你们都是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.42,0:16:26.01,Default,,0,0,0,,我为了拯救佐贺所千挑万选
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.01,0:16:28.22,Default,,0,0,0,,重获新生的丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.22,0:16:30.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你们法兰秀秀所成就的复仇之战
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.89,0:16:33.97,Default,,0,0,0,,将成为佐贺揭竿反抗的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.97,0:16:36.56,Default,,0,0,0,,伟大狼烟
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.18,0:16:41.69,Default,,0,0,0,,打什么喷嚏啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.69,0:16:42.56,Default,,0,0,0,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.57,0:16:43.69,Default,,0,0,0,,感觉好可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.69,0:16:45.32,Default,,0,0,0,,这收尾很差
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.32,0:16:46.61,Default,,0,0,0,,吵死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.16,0:16:57.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你是巽幸太郎先生对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.30,0:17:02.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我是佐贺志编辑部的大古场新太
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.42,0:17:05.50,Default,,0,0,0,,你写的报道我从没错过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.51,0:17:08.05,Default,,0,0,0,,一年前的演唱会真让人遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.05,0:17:08.97,Default,,0,0,0,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.97,0:17:12.05,Default,,0,0,0,,她们最近又开始活跃起来了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.52,0:17:16.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你会来这里是为了不忘记那时的失败吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.18,0:17:18.23,Default,,0,0,0,,针对我进行的采访我一概拒绝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.23,0:17:20.03,Default,,0,0,0,,只要在这行做久了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.04,0:17:22.98,Default,,0,0,0,,在各个业界都会认识不少人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.98,0:17:24.59,Default,,0,0,0,,即使如此这次确认真伪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.59,0:17:26.36,Default,,0,0,0,,还是费了我不少功夫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.59,0:17:29.28,Default,,0,0,0,,源樱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.28,0:17:30.74,Default,,0,0,0,,二阶堂咲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.74,0:17:32.11,Default,,0,0,0,,水野爱
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.12,0:17:33.41,Default,,0,0,0,,绀野纯子
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.41,0:17:35.83,Default,,0,0,0,,星川莉莉 也就是豪正雄
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.83,0:17:37.45,Default,,0,0,0,,山田妙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.45,0:17:39.87,Default,,0,0,0,,她们都已经过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.87,0:17:41.83,Default,,0,0,0,,很遗憾的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.83,0:17:44.25,Default,,0,0,0,,唯独5号我始终没掌握到情报
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.45,0:17:47.67,Default,,0,0,0,,请告诉我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.77,0:17:50.63,Default,,0,0,0,,她们到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.46,0:17:53.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我还拍到了这样的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.88,0:17:55.85,Default,,0,0,0,,还是说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.85,0:17:57.60,Default,,0,0,0,,要把坟墓挖出来看看呢？
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.61,0:18:00.56,Default,,0,0,0,,你为什么要将这写成报道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.56,0:18:04.19,Default,,0,0,0,,我要抨击你为了满足自己的私欲
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.19,0:18:07.48,Default,,0,0,0,,让已经死去的少女们 重新复活当偶像的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.48,0:18:09.40,Default,,0,0,0,,这样讲的话你能理解吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.17,0:18:12.87,Default,,0,0,0,,就算你继续保持沉默
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.87,0:18:14.47,Default,,0,0,0,,只要我将报道刊载出来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.47,0:18:16.24,Default,,0,0,0,,真相迟早会大白的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.24,0:18:20.08,Default,,0,0,0,,到那个时候社会大众又会怎么想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.63,0:18:23.08,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀下个月
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.08,0:18:25.04,Default,,0,0,0,,将在这站前体育场举行演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.83,0:18:27.09,Default,,0,0,0,,卷土重来的演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.09,0:18:28.46,Default,,0,0,0,,你疯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.46,0:18:31.13,Default,,0,0,0,,重蹈那种覆辙到底有什么意义
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.13,0:18:33.97,Default,,0,0,0,,别再将死者当成供人观赏取笑的玩物了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.70,0:18:36.89,Default,,0,0,0,,不管你打算撰写什么样的报道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.89,0:18:38.89,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀都不会停下脚步的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.89,0:18:44.27,Default,,0,0,0,,休想举行什么卷土重来演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.28,0:18:56.70,Default,,0,0,0,,没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.30,0:19:02.96,Default,,0,0,0,,看来这一次
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.96,0:19:05.96,Default,,0,0,0,,恐怕不能像之前的女高中生那样了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.96,0:19:10.42,Default,,0,0,0,,不如说这件事 更早之前就曝光发现都不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.42,0:19:13.13,Default,,0,0,0,,眼前的阻碍不是只有那个记者
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.80,0:19:15.34,Default,,0,0,0,,下次可能就不是受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.34,0:19:18.72,Default,,0,0,0,,或衣服被抢走就能了事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.72,0:19:20.72,Default,,0,0,0,,不管有谁来妨碍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.72,0:19:23.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我都一定要让这次站前体育馆成功
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.35,0:19:25.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我不会再重蹈同样的覆辙了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.22,0:19:27.52,Default,,0,0,0,,想不到十二年前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.52,0:19:29.07,Default,,0,0,0,,那个一脸忧郁
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.07,0:19:30.48,Default,,0,0,0,,内心病入膏肓的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.48,0:19:32.36,Default,,0,0,0,,竟然能走到现在这一步
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.36,0:19:34.82,Default,,0,0,0,,如果没有忧郁又病入膏肓的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.82,0:19:37.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我当时也不会相信你的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.28,0:19:40.16,Default,,0,0,0,,说什么已经和这片土地的诅咒战斗数千年
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.16,0:19:41.66,Default,,0,0,0,,什么不老不死
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.19,0:19:44.87,Default,,0,0,0,,什么能让死者起死回生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.48,0:19:47.29,Default,,0,0,0,,我不是实现你的愿望了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.29,0:19:48.63,Default,,0,0,0,,还没完
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.70,0:19:50.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我无论如何
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.62,0:19:52.95,Default,,0,0,0,,都一定会阻止你的预言发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.16,0:19:55.88,Default,,0,0,0,,在令和之初
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.88,0:19:58.39,Default,,0,0,0,,灭亡的危机将造访佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.39,0:19:59.89,Default,,0,0,0,,所谓的灭亡指的是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.89,0:20:02.01,Default,,0,0,0,,人们将不会再想到佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.02,0:20:05.43,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺将从人们的记忆中消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.99,0:20:06.89,Default,,0,0,0,,事实上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.89,0:20:09.69,Default,,0,0,0,,状况也因为人口外流而持续恶化著
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.69,0:20:10.65,Default,,0,0,0,,既然如此
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.65,0:20:12.22,Default,,0,0,0,,只要在佐贺打造出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.24,0:20:15.15,Default,,0,0,0,,能永远留在人们心中的存在就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.15,0:20:17.45,Default,,0,0,0,,因为诅咒而迎向死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.45,0:20:20.57,Default,,0,0,0,,原本应该能为佐贺带来繁荣的少女们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.58,0:20:24.08,Default,,0,0,0,,你找来了那些女孩组成偶像团体
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.08,0:20:25.83,Default,,0,0,0,,真亏你能想到这主意
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.83,0:20:28.58,Default,,0,0,0,,那个御船山丧尸乐园计划
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.58,0:20:30.96,Default,,0,0,0,,是丧尸乐园佐贺计划
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.96,0:20:32.13,Default,,0,0,0,,就是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.50,0:20:36.55,Default,,0,0,0,,推动这个人世的终究是人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.75,0:20:38.88,Default,,0,0,0,,你说错了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.95,0:20:41.30,Default,,0,0,0,,推动这个人世的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.30,0:20:43.47,Default,,0,0,0,,是人和丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.70,0:20:49.39,Default,,0,0,0,,从今夜到明天早上
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.40,0:20:52.61,Default,,0,0,0,,九州地区恐将降下局部性大雨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.80,0:20:56.44,Default,,0,0,0,,雨下得好大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.44,0:20:58.61,Default,,0,0,0,,幸太郎先生不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.61,0:21:00.03,Default,,0,0,0,,不需要担心他啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.03,0:21:01.32,Default,,0,0,0,,是这样的话就好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.32,0:21:04.53,Default,,0,0,0,,不然下次帮他喷上鞋子用的防水喷雾好了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.54,0:21:07.07,Default,,0,0,0,,我们最后的卷土重来之战
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.07,0:21:07.87,Default,,0,0,0,,明天就要开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.87,0:21:09.41,Default,,0,0,0,,要好好睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.73,0:21:18.30,Default,,0,0,0,,完成了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.30,0:21:20.72,Default,,0,0,0,,不是我自夸 这篇报道写得真不错
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.34,0:21:23.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我们下个月
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.35,0:21:25.31,Default,,0,0,0,,将在这站前体育场举行演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.20,0:21:28.85,Default,,0,0,0,,居然让死者做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.85,0:21:29.94,Default,,0,0,0,,你等著看
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.51,0:21:34.48,Default,,0,0,0,,不会吧 真的假的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.32,0:21:39.74,Default,,0,0,0,,这是…
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.79,0:23:26.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我是纯子
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.83,0:23:28.72,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然心里还是有一点不安
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.72,0:23:30.22,Default,,0,0,0,,不过除非碰上什么意外状况
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.22,0:23:33.31,Default,,0,0,0,,我想现在的我们 应该能好好一决胜负才对
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.31,0:23:36.06,Default,,0,0,0,,下一回的《佐贺偶像是传奇·卷土重来》第十一话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.06,0:23:37.94,Default,,0,0,0,,比方说只要有你在·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.94,0:23:39.02,Default,,0,0,0,,敬请期待

