[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Comment: Processed by 繁化姬 dict-001ce893-r978 @ 2021/09/23 03:08:18 | https://zhconvert.org
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Active Line: 6

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H00C14F0D,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: OPJP,A-OTF Kakushin Gyousho Std M,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H00262628,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: OPCN,方正正中黑_GBK,80,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H004C04CA,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,35,1
Style: EDJP,Source Han Serif CN,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: EDCN,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,2,15,15,15,1
Style: Tips,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H005A5A61,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0.5,8,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,@腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,130,&H005E03DD,&H000B24FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,7,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Next,腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,90,&H001004A4,&H000B24FF,&H00000000,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0,8,10,10,25,1
Style: Song1,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,15,1
Style: Song2,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: Song3,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.01,0:01:27.12,OPCN,,0,0,0,,就算一无所有也还有明天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.14,0:01:28.99,OPCN,,0,0,0,,跌落谷底 回归原点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.02,0:01:30.00,OPCN,,0,0,0,,这也是天性使然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.58,0:01:32.91,OPCN,,0,0,0,,哪怕燃烧殆尽也要实现目标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.94,0:01:35.22,OPCN,,0,0,0,,反击时刻现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.47,0:01:40.36,OPCN,,0,0,0,,无礼禁断
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.98,0:01:45.84,OPCN,,0,0,0,,彻头彻尾成就
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.84,0:01:48.68,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有人提出了挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.68,0:01:50.50,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 毅然奋起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.50,0:01:55.39,OPCN,,0,0,0,,你想要贯彻什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.87,0:01:59.63,OPCN,,0,0,0,,带着蜡烛的灯火
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.63,0:02:01.52,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 孤注一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.52,0:02:06.35,OPCN,,0,0,0,,向前进 然后终将燃烧殆尽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.88,0:02:10.37,OPCN,,0,0,0,,会是蝼蚁或亡者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.40,0:02:13.33,OPCN,,0,0,0,,还是闪烁的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.34,0:02:16.53,OPCN,,0,0,0,,赌上仅有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.53,0:02:20.35,OPCN,,0,0,0,,试图奋力挣扎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.78,0:02:24.86,OPCN,,0,0,0,,将命运吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.89,0:02:27.76,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如吞噬生命的实感般疾驰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.78,0:02:30.57,OPCN,,0,0,0,,不论他人如何掠夺 (奔跑吧)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.60,0:02:31.91,OPCN,,0,0,0,,从今以后 (不需要)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.94,0:02:33.97,OPCN,,0,0,0,,都再也不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.00,0:02:36.00,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如泉水涌出般
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.00,0:02:38.73,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有朝一日一起放声哭泣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.73,0:02:40.52,OPCN,,0,0,0,,燃起胧月篝火
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.52,0:02:43.21,OPCN,,0,0,0,,谁要去指望什么来生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.21,0:02:46.93,OPCN,,0,0,0,,顺从内心重新脱胎换骨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.93,0:02:48.97,OPCN,,0,0,0,,直到永远
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.97,0:02:52.15,OPCN,,0,0,0,,SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA

Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Song 1-----
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.55,0:20:17.19,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.19,0:20:25.10,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.20,0:20:31.78,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.83,0:20:46.30,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.08,0:20:50.60,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.60,0:20:52.77,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}深夜时分独自一人 (Wow )
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.78,0:20:54.87,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}重新涂抹深红艳唇 (Wow )
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.89,0:20:56.73,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}今晚会来还是不来?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.73,0:20:59.15,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}在等待中渐渐干枯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.15,0:21:01.23,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}撕下那一片又一片的花瓣
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.24,0:21:03.26,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}龙胆 龙胆
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.26,0:21:05.32,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}心急难耐仿佛要四分五裂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.32,0:21:07.53,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}有如被囚禁的小丑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.40,0:21:11.83,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.70,0:21:15.93,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.95,0:21:18.30,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}稍微装作八面玲珑 (Wow)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.32,0:21:20.41,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}传言随即就此开来 (Wow)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.44,0:21:22.30,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}与其就此悲惨堕落
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.32,0:21:24.74,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}不如用双手抢夺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.80,0:21:26.76,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}宿愿 (宿愿)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.76,0:21:29.14,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}爱恨交缠早已无法忍受
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.14,0:21:31.31,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}忧愁 (忧愁)
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.71,0:21:32.64,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.02,0:21:36.18,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}火热的蝴蝶乱舞令内心焦躁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.20,0:21:38.27,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}咒缚 咒缚 咒缚 咒缚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.29,0:21:40.42,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}渴望以赤红鲜血让你我结合
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.45,0:21:42.84,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}蔷薇 荆棘 荆棘 荆棘
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.90,0:21:45.28,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}越过那三瀬峠俵坂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.28,0:21:47.03,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}在地狱也要来见我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.03,0:21:48.99,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}吹散强风 躲避冰霰
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.99,0:21:49.82,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}快来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.83,0:21:51.83,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}要来? 不来? 快来 过来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.83,0:21:53.91,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}想在永远的甜蜜未来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.91,0:21:56.20,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}沉溺于彼此的怀抱中
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.77,0:22:00.25,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.01,0:22:04.46,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.40,0:22:08.72,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.54,0:22:12.75,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱 痴气乱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Title&Tips&Next-----
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.00,0:01:44.98,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord16\3c&H000000\shad0}佐贺事变 其之贰
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.00,0:01:44.98,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord10\shad0}佐贺事变 其之贰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.37,0:04:35.95,Tips,,0,0,0,,{\a5}注︰指佐贺筑地反射炉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.92,0:10:40.93,Tips,,0,0,0,,(长崎权令入县)
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.03,0:19:12.25,Tips,,0,0,0,,明治16年5月9日
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.25,0:19:16.10,Tips,,0,0,0,,在县内有志之士的请愿下\N佐贺县终于自长崎县独立
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.10,0:19:20.01,Tips,,0,0,0,,同年8月4日订立陆军治罪法\N禁止军人单方面进行处刑
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.01,0:19:24.64,Tips,,0,0,0,,同年8月13日\N最初的佐贺县议会举行
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.46,0:19:30.27,Default,,0,0,0,,(法兰秀秀佐贺事变演唱会 还有拍照会哦)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.73,0:23:40.05,Next,,0,0,0,,第十话 丧尸们将会如何复仇呢·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Main-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.00,0:00:08.61,Default,,0,0,0,,必须鼓舞佐贺的人民
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.64,0:00:10.66,Default,,0,0,0,,团结一致奋起对抗才行
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.73,0:00:13.28,Default,,0,0,0,,排除将国家占为己有的奸贼
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.30,0:00:14.33,Default,,0,0,0,,现在就是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.36,0:00:16.05,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺士族行动的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.08,0:00:17.29,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.18,0:00:20.17,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.17,0:00:22.89,Default,,0,0,0,,还让你特地送药过来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.10,0:00:25.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你爷爷的情况还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.88,0:00:27.67,Default,,0,0,0,,还是没什么好转
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.71,0:00:29.53,Default,,0,0,0,,几乎整天都在睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.07,0:00:31.18,Default,,0,0,0,,好不容易都看见
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.21,0:00:33.02,Default,,0,0,0,,取回佐贺的方向了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.89,0:00:36.78,Default,,0,0,0,,你的同伴增加不少了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.81,0:00:37.85,Default,,0,0,0,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.88,0:00:40.92,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在打算写一份请愿书
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.48,0:00:42.28,Default,,0,0,0,,就是这个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.30,0:00:43.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我们想向县令请愿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.34,0:00:45.26,Default,,0,0,0,,让佐贺县重新复活
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.29,0:00:46.29,Default,,0,0,0,,而且下次
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.31,0:00:47.79,Default,,0,0,0,,附近的村内长老们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.81,0:00:49.63,Default,,0,0,0,,也表示愿意听取我们的意见
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.49,0:00:52.79,Default,,0,0,0,,这下朝目标迈进一大步了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.82,0:00:53.52,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.55,0:00:55.58,Default,,0,0,0,,态度这么摇摆不定太不像话了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.61,0:00:57.72,Default,,0,0,0,,你这样还算是佐贺士族吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.74,0:00:58.99,Default,,0,0,0,,给我出来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.02,0:01:00.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我非好好教训你不可
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.86,0:01:03.13,Default,,0,0,0,,大家都太火气方刚了　　正合我意
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.27,0:01:04.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我先过去劝劝他们
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.71,0:01:05.29,Default,,0,0,0,,我现在就让你们知道
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.31,0:01:06.04,Default,,0,0,0,,你们有多肤浅
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.06,0:01:06.90,Default,,0,0,0,,这是对长者说话的态度吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.92,0:01:08.88,Default,,0,0,0,,各位 发生什么事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.91,0:01:10.66,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是实话实说罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.69,0:03:00.65,Default,,0,0,0,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.67,0:03:02.57,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么我要过来拍照啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.60,0:03:03.97,Default,,0,0,0,,有什么关系
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.00,0:03:04.75,Default,,0,0,0,,人家都说愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:06.74,Default,,0,0,0,,特别免费帮我们拍照了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.77,0:03:07.61,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.72,0:03:09.41,Default,,0,0,0,,如果说我们的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.44,0:03:12.02,Default,,0,0,0,,能为这家店招来客人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.05,0:03:14.76,Default,,0,0,0,,也算是拯救佐贺的一小步了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.41,0:03:16.45,Default,,0,0,0,,还是说
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.56,0:03:19.27,Default,,0,0,0,,你有什么不想被人拍的理由呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.16,0:03:23.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你…你该不会是…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.18,0:03:26.20,Default,,0,0,0,,以为灵魂会被吸走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.23,0:03:27.11,Default,,0,0,0,,才不是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.13,0:03:28.10,Default,,0,0,0,,放心吧放心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.12,0:03:29.72,Default,,0,0,0,,那只是迷信而已啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.74,0:03:31.00,Default,,0,0,0,,就说不是这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.03,0:03:32.57,Default,,0,0,0,,好了 不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.59,0:03:34.42,Default,,0,0,0,,请先静止不要动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.42,0:03:37.68,Default,,0,0,0,,要拍了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.19,0:03:40.52,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是个不错的回忆吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.63,0:03:41.75,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.41,0:03:46.06,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然时间早了点
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.09,0:03:47.21,Default,,0,0,0,,要去喝一杯吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.72,0:03:49.91,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起 我等一下有事要…
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.94,0:03:51.44,Default,,0,0,0,,百崎大人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.40,0:03:54.73,Default,,0,0,0,,我看下次再说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.76,0:03:55.92,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾小姐也是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.44,0:04:02.25,Default,,0,0,0,,旧佐贺藩士
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.43,0:04:04.97,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺战争的幸存者是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.50,0:04:07.93,Default,,0,0,0,,你最好也小心一点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.34,0:04:10.19,Default,,0,0,0,,这话是什么意思呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.85,0:04:22.34,Default,,0,0,0,,商人们总算答应了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.37,0:04:23.57,Default,,0,0,0,,我们的要求
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.60,0:04:24.60,Default,,0,0,0,,有了这些资金
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.63,0:04:26.11,Default,,0,0,0,,暂时就不必担心了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.14,0:04:27.97,Default,,0,0,0,,百崎大人那边该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.00,0:04:30.17,Default,,0,0,0,,姑且还是向他报告一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.19,0:04:31.57,Default,,0,0,0,,没这个必要
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.59,0:04:33.34,Default,,0,0,0,,先不说这个 真的可行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.37,0:04:35.95,Default,,0,0,0,,从筑地将锅岛的加农炮搬走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.98,0:04:38.69,Default,,0,0,0,,部署在长崎街道附近的计划
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.71,0:04:40.96,Default,,0,0,0,,有个商人向我们保证过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.64,0:04:46.03,Default,,0,0,0,,只能尽人事听天命了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.05,0:04:47.20,Default,,0,0,0,,将那些家伙视为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:49.00,Default,,0,0,0,,拯救佐贺的同志
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.03,0:04:52.20,Default,,0,0,0,,并接纳他们的人是喜一自己
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.33,0:04:55.75,Default,,0,0,0,,推动这个人世的终究是人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.77,0:04:57.81,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是因果
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.70,0:05:08.07,Default,,0,0,0,,因为你都不肯喝我送来的药
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.16,0:05:10.20,Default,,0,0,0,,让喜一伤透了脑筋呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.23,0:05:12.68,Default,,0,0,0,,没用的 我就是佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.70,0:05:15.13,Default,,0,0,0,,不 佐贺就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.36,0:05:16.25,Default,,0,0,0,,如果这里注定
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.28,0:05:17.92,Default,,0,0,0,,要走向灭亡的话
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.95,0:05:20.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我自然也将不复存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.06,0:05:22.27,Default,,0,0,0,,你的意思是喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.30,0:05:23.84,Default,,0,0,0,,再怎么拼命四处奔波
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.18,0:05:26.47,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺的命运也不会有改变吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.88,0:05:28.69,Default,,0,0,0,,人自有天命
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.80,0:05:30.52,Default,,0,0,0,,直到现在我也都能看见
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.55,0:05:32.14,Default,,0,0,0,,他身上那颗能拯救
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.16,0:05:34.00,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺命运的明星
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.35,0:05:35.23,Default,,0,0,0,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.27,0:05:39.27,Default,,0,0,0,,到头来能决定生死的还是人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.59,0:05:41.35,Default,,0,0,0,,现在的我也已经
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.37,0:05:44.14,Default,,0,0,0,,没有能借给他的力量了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.92,0:05:46.25,Default,,0,0,0,,把药喝了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.19,0:05:49.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我刚才都说了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.59,0:06:07.21,Default,,0,0,0,,请你每天一定都要服用
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.23,0:06:09.86,Default,,0,0,0,,直到将整箱药喝完为止
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.97,0:06:15.08,Default,,0,0,0,,请等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.11,0:06:16.94,Default,,0,0,0,,我们佐贺的怒恨
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.96,0:06:18.37,Default,,0,0,0,,不是凭那些请愿书
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.39,0:06:19.59,Default,,0,0,0,,有办法消除的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.62,0:06:21.42,Default,,0,0,0,,可是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.44,0:06:22.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我们做这些也不是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.89,0:06:24.28,Default,,0,0,0,,为了发起战争啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.30,0:06:26.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在唯一该做的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.15,0:06:27.69,Default,,0,0,0,,就是展开行动
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.92,0:06:30.51,Default,,0,0,0,,拜托你们再给我一点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.53,0:06:33.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我一定会拯救我们的佐贺的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.33,0:06:35.42,Default,,0,0,0,,你这年轻小辈怎么可能会懂
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.65,0:06:36.99,Default,,0,0,0,,你知道八年前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.12,0:06:38.75,Default,,0,0,0,,我们是抱着什么样的心情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.75,0:06:41.38,Default,,0,0,0,,眼睁睁看着佐贺走向灭亡的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.02,0:06:51.32,Default,,0,0,0,,已经够了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.40,0:06:54.79,Default,,0,0,0,,你已经很努力了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.21,0:06:56.14,Default,,0,0,0,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.17,0:06:58.12,Default,,0,0,0,,未来等待你的只有毁灭而已
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.13,0:07:02.28,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺战争的幸存者
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.30,0:07:03.53,Default,,0,0,0,,要是展开行动
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.86,0:07:05.57,Default,,0,0,0,,陆军绝不会坐视不管的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.06,0:07:09.10,Default,,0,0,0,,八年前的悲剧一定会再度重演
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.63,0:07:14.59,Default,,0,0,0,,其实你应该也注意到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.88,0:07:16.15,Default,,0,0,0,,光靠纯粹的理想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.17,0:07:17.80,Default,,0,0,0,,是无法改变世界的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.29,0:07:21.47,Default,,0,0,0,,可是要是我现在收手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.54,0:07:23.29,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺又该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.88,0:07:25.36,Default,,0,0,0,,因为觉得失去希望
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.38,0:07:27.60,Default,,0,0,0,,觉得佐贺已经无力回天
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.62,0:07:29.08,Default,,0,0,0,,所以大家都死心放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.10,0:07:31.77,Default,,0,0,0,,认为不会再有任何改变
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.84,0:07:33.72,Default,,0,0,0,,这样下去是不行的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.93,0:07:37.19,Default,,0,0,0,,不管出身如何
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.22,0:07:38.49,Default,,0,0,0,,不论处于什么立场
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.52,0:07:39.74,Default,,0,0,0,,大家都能自由选择
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.76,0:07:42.71,Default,,0,0,0,,活在自己理想的人生道路上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.88,0:07:44.23,Default,,0,0,0,,在努力争取到的未来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.23,0:07:45.73,Default,,0,0,0,,带着笑容相互扶持
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.76,0:07:48.45,Default,,0,0,0,,这就是我想重新取回的新佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.47,0:07:49.78,Default,,0,0,0,,不要再胡闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.04,0:07:52.28,Default,,0,0,0,,这种小鬼头的白日梦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.30,0:07:53.45,Default,,0,0,0,,你还想做多久
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.78,0:07:55.98,Default,,0,0,0,,这国家现在还不够成熟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.01,0:07:57.76,Default,,0,0,0,,还是太过扭曲而野蛮了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.86,0:07:59.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你只会被瞬间消灭
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.03,0:08:00.55,Default,,0,0,0,,就此结束掉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.80,0:08:03.60,Default,,0,0,0,,不要擅作主张结束掉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.73,0:08:06.24,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺根本就还没有开始啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.52,0:08:58.91,Default,,0,0,0,,再这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.94,0:09:00.77,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一将会被追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.07,0:09:01.92,Default,,0,0,0,,就算他没这个意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.95,0:09:02.86,Default,,0,0,0,,他还是成为了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.89,0:09:04.25,Default,,0,0,0,,引发内乱的导火线
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.36,0:09:07.45,Default,,0,0,0,,不如就先暂时离开佐贺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.05,0:09:09.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我之前不是在开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.03,0:09:11.91,Default,,0,0,0,,你和喜一一定能成为登对的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.93,0:09:13.00,Default,,0,0,0,,伊东先生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.05,0:09:14.30,Default,,0,0,0,,在伊东先生看来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.32,0:09:15.70,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一的志向难道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.73,0:09:18.39,Default,,0,0,0,,就只有这点程度吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.25,0:09:24.71,Default,,0,0,0,,他真是一个大傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.73,0:09:26.86,Default,,0,0,0,,做事笨拙又内向怕生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.92,0:09:28.92,Default,,0,0,0,,明明半点力量也没有
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.91,0:09:31.55,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我才会对那家伙…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.42,0:09:34.63,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.63,0:09:54.16,Default,,0,0,0,,拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.26,0:10:16.45,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢惠顾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.12,0:10:39.05,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在唯一该做的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.07,0:10:40.93,Default,,0,0,0,,就是展开行动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.16,0:10:58.31,Default,,0,0,0,,什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.23,0:11:45.59,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我才要你早点收手的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.69,0:12:09.09,Default,,0,0,0,,伊东 为什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.91,0:12:12.52,Default,,0,0,0,,你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.55,0:12:13.80,Default,,0,0,0,,你为什么要…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.82,0:12:15.07,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.26,0:12:18.55,Default,,0,0,0,,这样你还敢说你不会放弃吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.70,0:12:23.31,Default,,0,0,0,,监视潜伏在佐贺的逆贼是我的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.66,0:12:26.41,Default,,0,0,0,,如果只是小鬼的戏言那也就罢了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.90,0:12:29.52,Default,,0,0,0,,但既然你已经跨越了那条线
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.68,0:12:31.76,Default,,0,0,0,,伊…伊东
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.27,0:12:34.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我也只能这么做了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.32,0:12:40.06,Default,,0,0,0,,这国家还是太过扭曲而野蛮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.08,0:12:43.21,Default,,0,0,0,,因为找不到其他活下去的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.32,0:12:45.91,Default,,0,0,0,,别无选择的家伙到处都是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.11,0:12:49.16,Default,,0,0,0,,回答我啊 喜一
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.19,0:12:52.89,Default,,0,0,0,,快住手 伊东
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.58,0:13:20.71,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.97,0:13:34.24,Default,,0,0,0,,追兵应该很快就会过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.27,0:13:36.72,Default,,0,0,0,,你先暂时离开佐贺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.51,0:13:40.69,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么会变成这样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.87,0:13:45.81,Default,,0,0,0,,到头来我根本什么也不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.59,0:13:48.28,Default,,0,0,0,,所以伊东他…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.30,0:13:50.17,Default,,0,0,0,,还有其他同志们…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.19,0:13:51.65,Default,,0,0,0,,这全部都是我害的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.78,0:13:54.48,Default,,0,0,0,,因为我惹出这种麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.51,0:13:55.98,Default,,0,0,0,,才会害死大家
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.02,0:13:57.33,Default,,0,0,0,,还说什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.35,0:13:59.77,Default,,0,0,0,,说什么崭新的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.39,0:14:05.78,Default,,0,0,0,,请你快点逃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.11,0:14:09.18,Default,,0,0,0,,被追捕的人只有我一个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.20,0:14:11.04,Default,,0,0,0,,请你不要管我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.06,0:14:12.73,Default,,0,0,0,,快逃到其他地方去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.19,0:14:17.46,Default,,0,0,0,,别说这种没出息的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.54,0:14:18.64,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一先生的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.67,0:14:19.81,Default,,0,0,0,,确实很天真
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.92,0:14:20.95,Default,,0,0,0,,或许真的只是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.97,0:14:22.82,Default,,0,0,0,,孩童般的幼稚梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:24.13,Default,,0,0,0,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.15,0:14:25.86,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺因此而动了起来
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.88,0:14:27.26,Default,,0,0,0,,也是千真万确的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.30,0:14:28.50,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一先生必须
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.52,0:14:30.41,Default,,0,0,0,,背负起这个责任
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.98,0:14:34.84,Default,,0,0,0,,许多人因为喜一先生的话而死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.93,0:14:35.91,Default,,0,0,0,,再这样下去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.93,0:14:37.85,Default,,0,0,0,,大家的死就要白费了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.85,0:14:40.48,Default,,0,0,0,,除非喜一先生能实现目标
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.30,0:14:42.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你不是想取回佐贺吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.98,0:14:45.44,Default,,0,0,0,,不是想创造崭新的佐贺吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.44,0:14:46.36,Default,,0,0,0,,即使被人看不起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.38,0:14:47.69,Default,,0,0,0,,仍抱着信念向前冲
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.72,0:14:49.72,Default,,0,0,0,,一路上拼命活过留下的种种
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.75,0:14:50.67,Default,,0,0,0,,你忍心让它们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.70,0:14:51.98,Default,,0,0,0,,全都化为乌有吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.17,0:15:02.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你先越过三瀬峠
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.83,0:15:05.60,Default,,0,0,0,,再从博多搭船到长崎去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.16,0:15:07.84,Default,,0,0,0,,之后该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.87,0:15:09.39,Default,,0,0,0,,我全写在上面了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.45,0:15:11.77,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经事先拜托过
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.80,0:15:13.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我从前的旧识了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.33,0:15:16.20,Default,,0,0,0,,只要有了那些人的力量
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.22,0:15:18.22,Default,,0,0,0,,就算是政府的追兵
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.25,0:15:20.38,Default,,0,0,0,,也无法对喜一先生出手的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.00,0:15:26.88,Default,,0,0,0,,我所能做的也就只有这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.90,0:15:28.57,Default,,0,0,0,,活下来后该怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.59,0:15:30.37,Default,,0,0,0,,就要看喜一先生你自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.98,0:15:33.24,Default,,0,0,0,,请喜一先生让我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.27,0:15:36.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你创造的崭新佐贺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.80,0:15:50.75,Default,,0,0,0,,我要赌上我的一切对天发誓
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.77,0:15:51.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我一定会
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.90,0:15:54.89,Default,,0,0,0,,创造一个崭新的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.74,0:16:11.80,Default,,0,0,0,,真是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.83,0:16:14.75,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁还真是不得了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.61,0:16:17.87,Default,,0,0,0,,你的老公到底是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.19,0:16:22.51,Default,,0,0,0,,你听说过不拔刀的吉右卫门
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.53,0:16:23.86,Default,,0,0,0,,这号人物吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.22,0:16:26.52,Default,,0,0,0,,「日比谷之鬼」
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.50,0:16:33.64,Default,,0,0,0,,我也要拿出真本事了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.93,0:17:16.05,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.59,0:17:18.95,Default,,0,0,0,,把这差的下下签推给你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.10,0:17:20.14,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.73,0:17:25.11,Default,,0,0,0,,任谁都能随心所欲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.27,0:17:28.30,Default,,0,0,0,,自由生活的世界是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:10.22,Default,,0,0,0,,当你读到这封信的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.25,0:18:13.37,Default,,0,0,0,,我恐怕已经不在这个世上了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.41,0:18:16.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我的旧识们用名誉保证
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.49,0:18:19.16,Default,,0,0,0,,一定会好好保护喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.89,0:18:21.57,Default,,0,0,0,,既然流血事件已经发生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.60,0:18:23.39,Default,,0,0,0,,朝廷判断佐贺出现了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.41,0:18:24.73,Default,,0,0,0,,起义的征兆
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.95,0:18:25.72,Default,,0,0,0,,就必须有人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.74,0:18:28.58,Default,,0,0,0,,背起这个罪恶及责任才行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.43,0:18:31.32,Default,,0,0,0,,这起事件还有我这个人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.37,0:18:33.42,Default,,0,0,0,,恐怕都会被葬送在黑暗中
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.44,0:18:35.90,Default,,0,0,0,,让这一切变得从未发生过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.11,0:18:39.16,Default,,0,0,0,,如果喜一先生向你问起我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.21,0:18:40.27,Default,,0,0,0,,就请你告诉他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.30,0:18:42.75,Default,,0,0,0,,我后来平安离开佐贺了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.49,0:18:44.76,Default,,0,0,0,,然后
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.77,0:18:48.18,Default,,0,0,0,,如果说你真的是佐贺本身的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.22,0:18:50.01,Default,,0,0,0,,就请你为喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.03,0:18:53.16,Default,,0,0,0,,打造出的新佐贺指引方向吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.64,0:19:05.12,Default,,0,0,0,,后会有期
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.86,0:19:33.16,Default,,0,0,0,,有没有人看到我的帽子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.18,0:19:35.77,Default,,0,0,0,,彩排的时候你不是有戴着吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.79,0:19:37.63,Default,,0,0,0,,大概是被你放到哪去了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.65,0:19:39.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我刚刚真的有放在这里啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.11,0:19:42.03,Default,,0,0,0,,妙在吃什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.03,0:19:43.91,Default,,0,0,0,,难道说…　　小妙 不可以吃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.94,0:19:45.73,Default,,0,0,0,,那个不是花枝脚啦
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.88,0:19:49.58,Default,,0,0,0,,讨厌 全都是口水粘呼呼的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.63,0:19:51.92,Default,,0,0,0,,到底要拖拖拉拉到什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.94,0:19:54.43,Default,,0,0,0,,你们这群乐天极乐丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.46,0:19:57.16,Default,,0,0,0,,客人们都伸长颈在等你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.18,0:19:58.54,Default,,0,0,0,,好了 GoGoGo
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.56,0:20:00.34,Default,,0,0,0,,GoGoGoGoGoGo
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.37,0:20:01.09,Default,,0,0,0,,GoGo
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.11,0:20:02.65,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾雾 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.76,0:20:03.80,Default,,0,0,0,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.83,0:22:33.44,Default,,0,0,0,,这个时代感觉如何
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.68,0:22:35.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我过得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.37,0:22:36.58,Default,,0,0,0,,我果然还是喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.60,0:22:40.44,Default,,0,0,0,,在客人的面前唱歌跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.66,0:22:44.58,Default,,0,0,0,,那是叫什么来着? 砂岩鸟栖…
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.61,0:22:46.36,Default,,0,0,0,,是法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.54,0:22:47.92,Default,,0,0,0,,就是那个
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.64,0:22:49.72,Default,,0,0,0,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.74,0:22:51.09,Default,,0,0,0,,那家伙当初那样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.12,0:22:54.37,Default,,0,0,0,,拼命四处奔波也算是值得了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.77,0:22:56.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你说得没错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.41,0:22:59.58,Default,,0,0,0,,真的是非常感谢他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.68,0:23:05.09,Default,,0,0,0,,这一次轮到我了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.36,0:23:06.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我要在这崭新的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.02,0:23:08.87,Default,,0,0,0,,踏上我所选择的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.89,0:23:10.13,Default,,0,0,0,,继续走下去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.19,0:23:14.49,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟还有志同道合的伙伴
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.52,0:23:16.06,Default,,0,0,0,,陪伴在身边呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.07,0:23:27.10,Default,,0,0,0,,我是咲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.12,0:23:28.19,Default,,0,0,0,,真的是说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.22,0:23:29.58,Default,,0,0,0,,也敌不过大姐呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.61,0:23:30.79,Default,,0,0,0,,在成功卷土重来前
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:32.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我们绝不会输给任何人的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.22,0:23:32.91,Default,,0,0,0,,下一回的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.93,0:23:34.97,Default,,0,0,0,,《佐贺偶像是传奇·卷土重来》第十话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.97,0:23:37.23,Default,,0,0,0,,丧尸们将会如何复仇呢·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.25,0:23:38.86,Default,,0,0,0,,夜露死苦

