[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Comment: Processed by 繁化姬 dict-001ce893-r978 @ 2021/09/23 03:08:01 | https://zhconvert.org
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Active Line: 6

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H00C14F0D,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: OPJP,A-OTF Kakushin Gyousho Std M,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H00262628,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: OPCN,方正正中黑_GBK,80,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H004C04CA,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,35,1
Style: EDJP,Source Han Serif CN,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: EDCN,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,2,15,15,15,1
Style: Tips,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H005A5A61,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0.5,8,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,@腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,130,&H005E03DD,&H000B24FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,7,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Next,@腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,90,&H001004A4,&H000B24FF,&H00000000,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0,8,10,10,25,1
Style: Song1,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: Song2,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: Song3,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.06,0:01:48.19,OPCN,,0,0,0,,就算一无所有也还有明天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.19,0:01:50.04,OPCN,,0,0,0,,跌落谷底  回归原点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.04,0:01:51.02,OPCN,,0,0,0,,这也是天性使然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.61,0:01:53.95,OPCN,,0,0,0,,哪怕燃烧殆尽也要实现目标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.95,0:01:56.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,反击时刻现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.43,0:02:01.32,OPCN,,0,0,0,,无礼禁断
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.94,0:02:06.79,OPCN,,0,0,0,,彻头彻尾成就
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.79,0:02:09.64,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有人提出了挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.64,0:02:11.46,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 毅然奋起
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.46,0:02:16.35,OPCN,,0,0,0,,你想要贯彻什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.82,0:02:20.59,OPCN,,0,0,0,,带着蜡烛的灯火
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.59,0:02:22.47,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 孤注一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.47,0:02:27.31,OPCN,,0,0,0,,向前进 然后终将燃烧殆尽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.87,0:02:31.36,OPCN,,0,0,0,,会是蝼蚁或亡者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.36,0:02:34.29,OPCN,,0,0,0,,还是闪烁的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.29,0:02:37.49,OPCN,,0,0,0,,赌上仅有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.49,0:02:41.30,OPCN,,0,0,0,,试图奋力挣扎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.85,0:02:45.94,OPCN,,0,0,0,,将命运吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.94,0:02:48.81,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如吞噬生命的实感般疾驰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.81,0:02:51.60,OPCN,,0,0,0,,不论他人如何掠夺 (奔跑吧)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.60,0:02:52.92,OPCN,,0,0,0,,从今以后 (不需要)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.92,0:02:54.95,OPCN,,0,0,0,,都再也不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.95,0:02:56.96,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如泉水涌出般
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.96,0:02:59.69,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有朝一日一起放声哭泣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.69,0:03:01.48,OPCN,,0,0,0,,燃起胧月篝火
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.48,0:03:04.16,OPCN,,0,0,0,,谁要去指望什么来生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.16,0:03:07.89,OPCN,,0,0,0,,顺从内心重新脱胎换骨
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.89,0:03:09.93,OPCN,,0,0,0,,直到永远
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.93,0:03:13.09,OPCN,,0,0,0,,SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----EDCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.20,0:22:04.62,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}面对那如梦似幻的无尽日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.62,0:22:12.62,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}一起踏出找寻明日的旅程吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.27,0:22:24.42,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}回忆中的街道 改变了的景色
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.87,0:22:31.07,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}像个迷路的孩子般徘徊其中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.51,0:22:39.77,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}至少拥抱心胸的伤口向前进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.78,0:22:48.42,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}因为再也没有回头的理由了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.85,0:22:51.95,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}将梦想掌握手中
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.95,0:22:58.19,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}漫步于没有归处的日子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.19,0:23:05.37,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}为肯定这将是场无可取代的旅程前进吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.37,0:23:11.75,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}就算像发梦般遗忘了也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.75,0:23:13.94,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}我们不会忘记
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.94,0:23:16.93,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}哪怕夕阳西沉
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.93,0:23:21.20,EDCN,,0,0,0,,{\blur4\fad(300,300)}也要踏出步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Title&Tips&Next-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.72,0:00:08.32,Tips,,0,0,0,,(明治十四年秋天)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.06,0:02:05.94,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord16\3c&H000000\shad0}佐贺事变 其之壹
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.06,0:02:05.94,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord10\shad0}佐贺事变 其之壹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.58,0:03:18.87,Tips,,0,0,0,,(明治15年春天 旧佐贺城下)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.61,0:23:39.92,Next,,0,0,0,,{\an7\pos(460,20)\frz-90\fs140}第九话\N{\fs160}　佐贺事变\N{\fs140}　　　　其之贰
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Main-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.72,0:00:08.32,Default,,0,0,0,,你是说佐贺吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.32,0:00:09.28,Default,,0,0,0,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.28,0:00:11.66,Default,,0,0,0,,那里是日比谷大爷的故乡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.66,0:00:15.38,Default,,0,0,0,,听说他人在乡里的夫人很早就过世了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.38,0:00:17.66,Default,,0,0,0,,是一位很好相处的藩士
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.67,0:00:19.29,Default,,0,0,0,,不过真是太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.29,0:00:20.75,Default,,0,0,0,,对象是日比谷大爷的话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.75,0:00:22.96,Default,,0,0,0,,就算你经验再丰富也占不了上风了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.96,0:00:25.00,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟姜是老的辣  而且…
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.01,0:00:25.80,Default,,0,0,0,,算了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.80,0:00:28.65,Default,,0,0,0,,这方面我想你应该更清楚才对
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.80,0:00:33.10,Default,,0,0,0,,老爷  老板娘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.10,0:00:34.68,Default,,0,0,0,,非常感谢你们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.68,0:00:36.85,Default,,0,0,0,,承蒙你们许多照顾了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.85,0:00:38.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我还是第一次见到
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.30,0:00:40.44,Default,,0,0,0,,像你这样的花魁呢  夕雾
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.44,0:00:42.81,Default,,0,0,0,,我可不想再碰见第二次了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.82,0:00:43.82,Default,,0,0,0,,花魁居然因为
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.84,0:00:45.52,Default,,0,0,0,,人气过高而接不到客人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.52,0:00:47.19,Default,,0,0,0,,哪来这么离谱的传说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.19,0:00:49.67,Default,,0,0,0,,实在是非常抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.80,0:00:52.55,Default,,0,0,0,,你要好好过日子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.55,0:00:55.29,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我想你也用不着我们担心吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.64,0:01:07.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你们几个在这做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.36,0:01:08.72,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾姐姐
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.72,0:01:10.22,Default,,0,0,0,,赎身的事是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.22,0:01:12.02,Default,,0,0,0,,我们没办法再见面了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.02,0:01:13.97,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺是哪里  很远吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.97,0:01:14.80,Default,,0,0,0,,我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.80,0:01:16.85,Default,,0,0,0,,我还想向你学习
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.87,0:01:18.48,Default,,0,0,0,,更多跳舞和唱歌的技巧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.75,0:01:20.81,Default,,0,0,0,,好了好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.81,0:01:21.25,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.28,0:01:24.36,Default,,0,0,0,,准备迎接可喜可贺的新人生了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.36,0:01:25.86,Default,,0,0,0,,这有什么好哭的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.45,0:01:27.48,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.49,0:01:30.11,Default,,0,0,0,,请你们笑着为我送行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.89,0:01:34.91,Default,,0,0,0,,不管佐贺距离这里有多遥远
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.91,0:01:37.87,Default,,0,0,0,,我的内心也永远会想着大家的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.44,0:01:41.96,Default,,0,0,0,,不过老实说佐贺已经不存在了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.26,0:03:34.49,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾师父
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.49,0:03:36.61,Default,,0,0,0,,不管什么时候看都好漂亮哦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.61,0:03:39.20,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟她是传说中的花魁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.20,0:03:40.78,Default,,0,0,0,,是什么传说呀
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.78,0:03:42.66,Default,,0,0,0,,这你就不必知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.22,0:03:50.25,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁在众人依依不舍下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.28,0:03:51.74,Default,,0,0,0,,离开游廓后又过了几个月
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.74,0:03:56.26,Default,,0,0,0,,将她赎去的政府高官突然因病倒下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.27,0:03:58.51,Default,,0,0,0,,就这么离开了人世
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.74,0:04:01.88,Default,,0,0,0,,依照其生前的遗嘱
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.88,0:04:03.93,Default,,0,0,0,,她获得了一部分的遗产
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.93,0:04:06.60,Default,,0,0,0,,得以高枕无忧地度过余生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.60,0:04:07.89,Default,,0,0,0,,但在这无亲无故
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.90,0:04:10.48,Default,,0,0,0,,没有任何熟识之人的街道上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.48,0:04:14.48,Default,,0,0,0,,她将就此度过一生已成为定局
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.65,0:04:22.37,Default,,0,0,0,,再怎么说她可是传说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.37,0:04:25.76,Default,,0,0,0,,她和上芦町的那些人格调可不一样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.77,0:04:28.21,Default,,0,0,0,,不知道她都过着什么样的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.21,0:04:30.58,Default,,0,0,0,,来来来  欢迎来坐坐
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.58,0:04:32.63,Default,,0,0,0,,馒头  团子和红豆汤
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.63,0:04:34.75,Default,,0,0,0,,来来来  快来买哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.39,0:04:41.01,Default,,0,0,0,,时候已到
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.01,0:04:43.01,Default,,0,0,0,,现在是我们奋起的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.01,0:04:43.89,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.89,0:04:46.35,Default,,0,0,0,,一起夺回佐贺吧  佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.35,0:04:47.56,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.06,0:04:51.25,Default,,0,0,0,,这是在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.25,0:04:52.21,Default,,0,0,0,,快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.13,0:04:55.44,Default,,0,0,0,,快来看看哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.44,0:04:58.24,Default,,0,0,0,,走过路过别错过
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.51,0:05:02.87,Default,,0,0,0,,新五郎剧团的巡回公演
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.87,0:05:04.28,Default,,0,0,0,,仅限七天的盛大演出
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.28,0:05:06.41,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺  佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.41,0:05:09.12,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺来了哦  佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.12,0:05:10.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你这家伙是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.68,0:05:15.04,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.21,0:05:24.01,Default,,0,0,0,,搞什么鬼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.01,0:05:27.35,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.11,0:05:34.75,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么又是你啊  百崎喜一
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.75,0:05:37.48,Default,,0,0,0,,别想逃  乖乖就范吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.30,0:05:44.70,Default,,0,0,0,,应该可以当成面纸用吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.56,0:05:48.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.70,0:05:51.75,Default,,0,0,0,,一天到晚都在给大家添麻烦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.75,0:05:53.21,Default,,0,0,0,,别再给我找麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.21,0:05:55.29,Default,,0,0,0,,要捉捕吗  要我捉捕你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.29,0:05:57.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是想把佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.42,0:05:58.96,Default,,0,0,0,,有人抢劫  别让他逃了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.00,0:06:02.30,Default,,0,0,0,,在我回来前你别给我乱跑
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.30,0:06:04.26,Default,,0,0,0,,抢劫犯在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.46,0:06:11.81,Default,,0,0,0,,伊东
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.81,0:06:15.02,Default,,0,0,0,,你真是学不会教训
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.88,0:06:17.86,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺在这个时代
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.86,0:06:20.97,Default,,0,0,0,,被明治政府视为难以治理的县区
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.99,0:06:22.32,Default,,0,0,0,,存在备受关注
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.47,0:06:25.07,Default,,0,0,0,,过去在幕府末年
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.07,0:06:26.89,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺抢在其他诸藩之前
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.91,0:06:27.99,Default,,0,0,0,,率先实现西化
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.99,0:06:31.08,Default,,0,0,0,,在维新运动扮演着重要角色
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.08,0:06:32.08,Default,,0,0,0,,然而
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.08,0:06:33.45,Default,,0,0,0,,自从明治七年
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.45,0:06:35.92,Default,,0,0,0,,爆发士族叛乱并败北之后
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.92,0:06:37.71,Default,,0,0,0,,其荣光就此一落千丈
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.32,0:06:40.54,Default,,0,0,0,,至明治九年佐贺县
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.55,0:06:44.30,Default,,0,0,0,,被三潴及长崎两县分割并统合
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.30,0:06:45.58,Default,,0,0,0,,到最后其名字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.61,0:06:47.97,Default,,0,0,0,,终于从地图上消失了踪影
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.10,0:06:52.07,Default,,0,0,0,,劝你最好该适可而止了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.28,0:06:56.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我也无法保证每次都救得了你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.90,0:06:59.88,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是想把消失的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.91,0:07:01.69,Default,,0,0,0,,抢回来而已啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.69,0:07:03.64,Default,,0,0,0,,你一个人在那胡闹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.67,0:07:05.61,Default,,0,0,0,,也不会有任何改变的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.61,0:07:08.20,Default,,0,0,0,,朝廷目前还是对佐贺保持警戒
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.40,0:07:11.45,Default,,0,0,0,,大家也都不想
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.48,0:07:13.79,Default,,0,0,0,,再看到佐贺战争的悲剧重演了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.79,0:07:16.04,Default,,0,0,0,,我又不是想引发战争
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.04,0:07:18.08,Default,,0,0,0,,大家眼中看来可不是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.09,0:07:21.04,Default,,0,0,0,,再说就算你真的取回了佐贺之名
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.04,0:07:22.59,Default,,0,0,0,,之后又能怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.68,0:07:25.05,Default,,0,0,0,,这…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.05,0:07:26.59,Default,,0,0,0,,算了算了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.59,0:07:28.93,Default,,0,0,0,,这种复杂的话题先暂且打住
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.93,0:07:31.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我看我们下次一起去赏樱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.47,0:07:34.14,Default,,0,0,0,,比已经不复存在的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.14,0:07:37.10,Default,,0,0,0,,还要更有魅力的漂亮艺妓多的是哦
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.10,0:07:40.65,Default,,0,0,0,,我对那种事情又没有…
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.73,0:07:44.32,Default,,0,0,0,,我的肉呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.91,0:07:45.86,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢招待
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.46,0:07:47.95,Default,,0,0,0,,过来啊过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.95,0:07:50.74,Default,,0,0,0,,有本事的家伙给我放马过来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.29,0:07:55.53,Default,,0,0,0,,师父总是留在家里头实在太可惜了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.53,0:07:57.12,Default,,0,0,0,,现在是赏樱的季节
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.12,0:07:59.32,Default,,0,0,0,,让我们介绍你几个赏樱的景点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.38,0:08:06.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我希望你能接触外面的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.11,0:09:06.19,Default,,0,0,0,,这是…那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.32,0:09:10.61,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你帮我捡到
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.78,0:09:13.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我才刚买没多久而已
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.67,0:09:20.64,Default,,0,0,0,,让开让开让开让开让开
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.43,0:09:22.42,Default,,0,0,0,,危险
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.00,0:09:38.64,Default,,0,0,0,,你不要紧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.55,0:09:46.86,Default,,0,0,0,,那个…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.43,0:09:50.44,Default,,0,0,0,,请用
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.00,0:09:52.15,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.56,0:09:56.58,Default,,0,0,0,,这是我的…
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.05,0:10:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,原来是这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.00,0:10:03.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我把它当成面纸了  真对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.44,0:10:09.76,Default,,0,0,0,,赶快回去把衣服换了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.40,0:10:20.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你在做什么啊  喜一
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.99,0:10:23.19,Default,,0,0,0,,是天女
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.65,0:10:27.57,Default,,0,0,0,,我猜她大概是那个吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.57,0:10:30.36,Default,,0,0,0,,去年年底被人赎身来到佐贺的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.36,0:10:31.86,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.86,0:10:33.57,Default,,0,0,0,,传说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.57,0:10:34.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我说你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.87,0:10:36.70,Default,,0,0,0,,如果你真想取回佐贺的话
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.70,0:10:38.70,Default,,0,0,0,,至少该打听些街头巷尾的传闻吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.62,0:10:42.33,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁夕雾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.33,0:10:44.79,Default,,0,0,0,,人称江户开府以来的奇迹
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.79,0:10:46.36,Default,,0,0,0,,男人自然不在话下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.39,0:10:47.96,Default,,0,0,0,,同时也深受女人憧憬
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.96,0:10:50.30,Default,,0,0,0,,因为客人你争我夺的结果
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.30,0:10:52.84,Default,,0,0,0,,导致价码无止尽地向上提高
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.84,0:10:55.22,Default,,0,0,0,,到最后变得根本没人请得起
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.15,0:10:58.80,Default,,0,0,0,,听说连维新元老也纷纷彼此斗争
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.81,0:11:02.06,Default,,0,0,0,,导致明治朝廷濒临崩坏
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.06,0:11:04.85,Default,,0,0,0,,那样的人竟然会来佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.65,0:11:06.48,Default,,0,0,0,,别迷上她了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.48,0:11:07.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你少乱讲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.69,0:11:12.38,Default,,0,0,0,,她不是你担负得起的对象
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.38,0:11:14.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你们生活的世界是不一样的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.93,0:11:20.49,Default,,0,0,0,,生活的世界不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.79,0:11:57.03,Default,,0,0,0,,你是之前的…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.52,0:12:08.46,Default,,0,0,0,,结果反而让你为我费心了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.46,0:12:12.22,Default,,0,0,0,,不  这也没什么大不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.23,0:12:14.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我就心怀感激地收下了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.21,0:12:17.09,Default,,0,0,0,,不过  我想你差不多该回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.54,0:12:20.68,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是为了你好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.56,0:12:28.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我…我不会在意的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.91,0:12:32.68,Default,,0,0,0,,不管是生活的世界不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.68,0:12:34.53,Default,,0,0,0,,还是怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.53,0:12:36.23,Default,,0,0,0,,那些乱七八糟的事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.23,0:12:37.82,Default,,0,0,0,,在我们的佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.82,0:12:40.99,Default,,0,0,0,,在佐贺…在佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.96,0:12:43.66,Default,,0,0,0,,在佐贺…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.95,0:13:09.52,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.52,0:13:12.44,Default,,0,0,0,,这里有位叫百崎喜一的先生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.71,0:13:20.04,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.08,0:13:22.78,Default,,0,0,0,,我就是佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.78,0:13:25.41,Default,,0,0,0,,不对  佐贺就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.43,0:13:32.63,Default,,0,0,0,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.63,0:13:33.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你不要紧吧  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.98,0:13:36.00,Default,,0,0,0,,爷爷  你又擅自跑出来…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.46,0:13:42.00,Default,,0,0,0,,这些是能治感冒
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.03,0:13:45.35,Default,,0,0,0,,还可以治百病  滋养身体的中药
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.35,0:13:48.22,Default,,0,0,0,,是我请以前认识的人送来的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.23,0:13:50.77,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思  让你专程…
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:52.94,Default,,0,0,0,,你之前明明发高烧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.94,0:13:55.47,Default,,0,0,0,,还特地过来向我打招呼
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.47,0:13:56.82,Default,,0,0,0,,实在是很过意不去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.82,0:14:00.61,Default,,0,0,0,,那也是我自己擅作主张…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.25,0:14:02.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我觉得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.99,0:14:04.78,Default,,0,0,0,,除了学跳舞的徒弟之外
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.78,0:14:06.58,Default,,0,0,0,,这还是我来到佐贺后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.58,0:14:08.74,Default,,0,0,0,,第一次有人前来拜访我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.93,0:14:13.16,Default,,0,0,0,,刚才爷爷让你看笑话了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.04,0:14:16.42,Default,,0,0,0,,爷爷他是个有点…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.42,0:14:19.00,Default,,0,0,0,,他是个不可思议的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.01,0:14:21.17,Default,,0,0,0,,他是这几年突然变成这样的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.84,0:14:23.01,Default,,0,0,0,,他一直说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.03,0:14:25.97,Default,,0,0,0,,他无法忍受佐贺连名字都要消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.73,0:14:28.61,Default,,0,0,0,,还说什么"我要是有以前的力量"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.61,0:14:32.77,Default,,0,0,0,,"要让死人复活根本就易如反掌"之类的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.97,0:14:35.69,Default,,0,0,0,,那是大概八年前的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.69,0:14:37.02,Default,,0,0,0,,在佐贺这片土地上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.02,0:14:38.69,Default,,0,0,0,,曾发生过一场大战
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.69,0:14:40.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我的父亲也在战争中死去了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.39,0:14:45.20,Default,,0,0,0,,在那之后无家可归的我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.20,0:14:48.12,Default,,0,0,0,,一个人独自蹲坐在荒野中
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.60,0:14:50.54,Default,,0,0,0,,要不是爷爷收留我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.54,0:14:51.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我现在肯定已经…
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.64,0:14:55.96,Default,,0,0,0,,爷爷对我的恩情真的是还也还不清
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.96,0:14:58.34,Default,,0,0,0,,不过爷爷他对我说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.34,0:15:00.50,Default,,0,0,0,,"我只希望你做一件事"
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.50,0:15:02.34,Default,,0,0,0,,"那就是拯救佐贺"
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.04,0:15:05.88,Default,,0,0,0,,一开始我实在不懂他的意思
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.89,0:15:06.97,Default,,0,0,0,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.97,0:15:09.16,Default,,0,0,0,,现在佐贺不但连名字都消失了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.16,0:15:11.08,Default,,0,0,0,,父亲大人想守护的事物
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.10,0:15:12.43,Default,,0,0,0,,都开始逐渐消失
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.37,0:15:16.02,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺在大家的心中慢慢死去
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.69,0:15:18.60,Default,,0,0,0,,这些事让我没办法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.55,0:15:21.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我想爷爷当初会收留我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.47,0:15:23.24,Default,,0,0,0,,一定是命运的安排
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.24,0:15:25.86,Default,,0,0,0,,为了让我找到我的生存之道
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.11,0:15:30.45,Default,,0,0,0,,夕雾
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.45,0:15:34.00,Default,,0,0,0,,这就是你今后将生活的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.57,0:15:40.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我觉得我现在终于找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.18,0:15:43.42,Default,,0,0,0,,我真正应该去做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.07,0:15:47.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我想打造一个崭新的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.14,0:15:48.59,Default,,0,0,0,,一个既不分男女
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.59,0:15:51.60,Default,,0,0,0,,也不分士农工商
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.60,0:15:55.27,Default,,0,0,0,,每个人都能选择自己的道路
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.27,0:15:57.64,Default,,0,0,0,,带着笑容活出自我的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.68,0:16:02.48,Default,,0,0,0,,那真是个美妙的梦想呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.64,0:16:09.78,Default,,0,0,0,,拜托了  拜托大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.78,0:16:13.12,Default,,0,0,0,,要捉捕吗  要我捉捕你吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.31,0:16:16.16,Default,,0,0,0,,别吓我啦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.16,0:16:18.46,Default,,0,0,0,,你这小子还真学不乖耶
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.23,0:16:24.94,Default,,0,0,0,,那个…我拜托人重新写过了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.94,0:16:27.38,Default,,0,0,0,,内容也是对方愿意跟我商量而改写的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.63,0:16:33.76,Default,,0,0,0,,好乖好乖
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.13,0:16:54.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是送鱼来而已
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.82,0:16:59.25,Default,,0,0,0,,真是不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.25,0:17:02.63,Default,,0,0,0,,因为刚才的气息相当强烈
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.63,0:17:04.21,Default,,0,0,0,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.21,0:17:06.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.43,0:17:10.18,Default,,0,0,0,,伊东  你这么早就来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.18,0:17:13.76,Default,,0,0,0,,因为我想早点见见传说中的花魁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.76,0:17:16.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你看  这就是我之前提过的大鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.47,0:17:18.02,Default,,0,0,0,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.02,0:17:21.31,Default,,0,0,0,,福所江川真的能钓到这么大的鱼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.83,0:17:40.71,Default,,0,0,0,,好吃
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.18,0:17:44.04,Default,,0,0,0,,传说中的花魁连料理都会做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.65,0:17:46.80,Default,,0,0,0,,将我赎来这里的大爷
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.80,0:17:48.67,Default,,0,0,0,,教了我许多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.34,0:17:50.81,Default,,0,0,0,,他说这是为了让我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.83,0:17:52.30,Default,,0,0,0,,在外面的世界生活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.03,0:17:55.39,Default,,0,0,0,,"许多东西"是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.63,0:18:00.39,Default,,0,0,0,,我看你也该收手了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.23,0:18:02.27,Default,,0,0,0,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.27,0:18:04.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你的脑袋本来就不算差
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.81,0:18:06.98,Default,,0,0,0,,看是要当学者还是医生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.98,0:18:08.23,Default,,0,0,0,,如果真想救人的话
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.23,0:18:10.57,Default,,0,0,0,,不是还有这些更脚踏实地的方法吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.19,0:18:14.36,Default,,0,0,0,,不必搞什么夺回佐贺的大事业吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.69,0:18:25.00,Default,,0,0,0,,都好不容易遇见了有缘人了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.00,0:18:26.63,Default,,0,0,0,,你好好考虑一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.63,0:18:27.79,Default,,0,0,0,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.80,0:18:30.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我看你干脆就建立家庭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.20,0:18:32.55,Default,,0,0,0,,只要成为一家之主
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.55,0:18:34.13,Default,,0,0,0,,就会产生责任感了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.97,0:18:36.26,Default,,0,0,0,,你们很登对哦
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.60,0:18:42.90,Default,,0,0,0,,你你你你你在…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.90,0:18:44.36,Default,,0,0,0,,你在说什…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.36,0:18:45.52,Default,,0,0,0,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.52,0:18:48.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你这家伙到底…到底乱说什么…
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.58,0:18:55.78,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.84,0:18:59.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你振作一点啊  喜一先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.30,0:19:03.33,Default,,0,0,0,,真服了这小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.59,0:19:08.63,Default,,0,0,0,,不必了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.00,0:19:14.22,Default,,0,0,0,,你也来一杯吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.22,0:19:15.72,Default,,0,0,0,,不  我没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.45,0:19:24.85,Default,,0,0,0,,伊东先生
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.85,0:19:27.85,Default,,0,0,0,,你和喜一先生认识很久了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.46,0:19:30.62,Default,,0,0,0,,大概是两年多前的事了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.62,0:19:32.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我听说有个老爱发一些
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.86,0:19:35.07,Default,,0,0,0,,莫名其妙传单的怪人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.07,0:19:36.82,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我才打算捉弄他一下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.51,0:19:39.45,Default,,0,0,0,,明明大家都避而远之
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.45,0:19:42.12,Default,,0,0,0,,根本没人愿意停下脚步的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.12,0:19:45.71,Default,,0,0,0,,但他还是拼命地持续着
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.29,0:19:48.63,Default,,0,0,0,,明明还有其他更值得做的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.52,0:19:51.67,Default,,0,0,0,,他真是个傻小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.78,0:19:57.63,Default,,0,0,0,,这个国家已经变了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.64,0:19:59.85,Default,,0,0,0,,以后也将继续改变下去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.85,0:20:04.02,Default,,0,0,0,,执著于旧名又能对未来带来什么
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.02,0:20:06.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我想喜一先生想重新取回的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.27,0:20:08.27,Default,,0,0,0,,一定不是旧的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.27,0:20:11.19,Default,,0,0,0,,而是起死回生的佐贺吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.27,0:20:16.40,Default,,0,0,0,,这也许是个粗糙不堪的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.40,0:20:19.99,Default,,0,0,0,,但是我也希望能亲眼看看
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.99,0:20:21.95,Default,,0,0,0,,喜一先生所说的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.88,0:20:31.33,Default,,0,0,0,,不过总有一天
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.34,0:20:32.84,Default,,0,0,0,,这家伙那颗率直的心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.84,0:20:34.50,Default,,0,0,0,,一定会遭受到挫折的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.34,0:20:39.30,Default,,0,0,0,,这个国家现在还是太过扭曲而野蛮了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.22,0:20:42.51,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢招待
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.51,0:20:43.72,Default,,0,0,0,,我玩得很开心
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.69,0:20:57.19,Default,,0,0,0,,拜托大家了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.20,0:20:58.78,Default,,0,0,0,,请救救佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.61,0:21:07.04,Default,,0,0,0,,那个…请问…
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.04,0:21:09.44,Default,,0,0,0,,可以将详情告诉我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.44,0:21:12.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我们也想重新取回属于我们的佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.76,0:23:27.20,Default,,0,0,0,,我是夕雾
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.20,0:23:29.89,Default,,0,0,0,,看见为信念赌上一切的男士
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.89,0:23:31.77,Default,,0,0,0,,总会让人内心激昂呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.77,0:23:32.45,Default,,0,0,0,,下一回的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.48,0:23:34.56,Default,,0,0,0,,《佐贺偶像是传奇·卷土重来》第九话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.56,0:23:36.65,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺事变·其之贰
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.65,0:23:38.19,Default,,0,0,0,,各位后会有期
