[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Comment: Processed by 繁化姬 dict-001ce893-r978 @ 2021/09/23 03:03:59 | https://zhconvert.org
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None
PlayResX: 1920
PlayResY: 1080

[Aegisub Project Garbage]
Active Line: 6

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H00C14F0D,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1
Style: OPJP,A-OTF Kakushin Gyousho Std M,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H00262628,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: OPCN,方正正中黑_GBK,80,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H004C04CA,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,35,1
Style: EDJP,Source Han Serif CN,60,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,8,0,0,15,1
Style: EDCN,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,&H003B3B3E,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0,2,0,0,15,1
Style: Tips,方正正中黑_GBK,68,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H005A5A61,&H00101010,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2.5,0.5,8,30,30,30,1
Style: Title,@腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,130,&H005E03DD,&H000B24FF,&H00FFFFFF,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,7,0,1,10,10,10,1
Style: Next,腾祥伯当行楷GB18030,90,&H001004A4,&H000B24FF,&H00000000,&H00101010,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0,8,10,10,25,1
Style: Song1,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,5,5,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Song2,Source Han Serif CN,75,&H00FFFFFF,&H000B24FF,&H003939D7,&H00101010,-1,-1,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,3,0,2,10,10,35,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----OPCN-----
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.00,0:01:31.11,OPCN,,0,0,0,,就算一无所有也还有明天
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.11,0:01:32.96,OPCN,,0,0,0,,跌落谷底  回归原点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.96,0:01:33.94,OPCN,,0,0,0,,这也是天性使然
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.53,0:01:36.87,OPCN,,0,0,0,,哪怕燃烧殆尽也要实现目标
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.87,0:01:39.15,OPCN,,0,0,0,,反击时刻现在开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.35,0:01:44.24,OPCN,,0,0,0,,无礼禁断
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.86,0:01:49.72,OPCN,,0,0,0,,彻头彻尾成就
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.72,0:01:52.56,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有人提出了挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.56,0:01:54.38,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 毅然奋起
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.38,0:01:59.27,OPCN,,0,0,0,,你想要贯彻什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.75,0:02:03.51,OPCN,,0,0,0,,带着蜡烛的灯火
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.51,0:02:05.40,OPCN,,0,0,0,,Just Just 孤注一掷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.40,0:02:10.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,向前进 然后终将燃烧殆尽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.79,0:02:14.28,OPCN,,0,0,0,,会是蝼蚁或亡者
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.28,0:02:17.21,OPCN,,0,0,0,,还是闪烁的星星
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.22,0:02:20.41,OPCN,,0,0,0,,赌上仅有的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.41,0:02:24.23,OPCN,,0,0,0,,试图奋力挣扎吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.78,0:02:28.86,OPCN,,0,0,0,,将命运吞噬
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.86,0:02:31.73,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如吞噬生命的实感般疾驰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.73,0:02:34.52,OPCN,,0,0,0,,不论他人如何掠夺 (奔跑吧)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.52,0:02:35.84,OPCN,,0,0,0,,从今以后 (不需要)
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.84,0:02:37.88,OPCN,,0,0,0,,都再也不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.88,0:02:39.88,OPCN,,0,0,0,,如泉水涌出般
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.88,0:02:42.61,OPCN,,0,0,0,,有朝一日一起放声哭泣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.61,0:02:44.40,OPCN,,0,0,0,,燃起胧月篝火
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.40,0:02:47.09,OPCN,,0,0,0,,谁要去指望什么来生呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.09,0:02:50.81,OPCN,,0,0,0,,顺从内心重新脱胎换骨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.81,0:02:52.85,OPCN,,0,0,0,,直到永远
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.85,0:02:56.01,OPCN,,0,0,0,,SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA SAGA
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Song 1-----
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.96,0:21:40.98,Default,,0,0,0,,和我们一起大声呼喊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.23,0:22:47.28,Default,,0,0,0,,那么接下来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.44,0:21:43.81,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}这整个世界全都是敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.81,0:21:46.80,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}不屑地对一切吐出唾液
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.80,0:21:48.57,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}即使如此在这甜蜜的夜晚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.57,0:21:52.94,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}感觉似乎会发生什么大事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.94,0:21:58.46,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}与和我相似的你吃着免下车的餐点
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.46,0:22:01.75,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}就连夜色渐明的天空光芒
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.75,0:22:04.86,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}你也火冒三丈地瞪眼望着
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.86,0:22:06.36,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}Ah 不过呢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.36,0:22:08.50,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}总有一天肯定会懂的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.79,0:22:12.21,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}Ah 没有错
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.21,0:22:14.45,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}我知道你一定会改变
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.08,0:22:19.04,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}相信你必定会成为
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.04,0:22:22.69,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}能拥抱过去自己的那个自己的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.38,0:22:29.23,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}你讨厌强风吹袭的日子吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.23,0:22:31.65,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}只不过是这点程度而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.66,0:22:34.37,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}别开玩笑了好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.19,0:22:41.56,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}就像让爱永垂不朽那般
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.56,0:22:46.23,Song1,,0,0,0,,{\fad(200,200)}你只要继续做你自己就可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Title&Tips&Next-----
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.98,0:01:49.05,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord16\3c&H000000\shad0}快要坏掉的收音机 佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.98,0:01:49.05,OPCN,,0,0,0,,{\pos(960,720)\fs90\frx-30\bord10\shad0}快要坏掉的收音机 佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.45,0:04:30.92,Tips,,0,0,0,,(电视台主持)
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.77,0:06:44.15,Default,,0,0,0,,(恰到好处地拜托大家了)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.01,0:07:12.40,Default,,0,0,0,,(恰到好处地绕一绕)
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.69,0:07:16.58,Default,,0,0,0,,(木刀)
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.22,0:08:22.57,Default,,0,0,0,,(恰到好处地去拜结缘之神)
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.13,0:08:34.26,Default,,0,0,0,,(恰到好处地进本殿参拜)
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.41,0:08:47.06,Default,,0,0,0,,(恰到好处地收尾)
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.10,0:23:40.02,Next,,0,0,0,,第三话 爱与青春的木吉他·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,-----Main-----
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:00.00,Default,,0,0,0,,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.83,0:00:02.82,Default,,0,0,0,,上一回的《佐贺偶像是传奇·卷土重来》
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.82,0:00:04.03,Default,,0,0,0,,在站前体育场办演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.06,0:00:05.32,Default,,0,0,0,,最后大失败的我们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.32,0:00:06.88,Default,,0,0,0,,一边打工一边等待
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.91,0:00:08.31,Default,,0,0,0,,变长发的幸太郎先生回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.31,0:00:09.42,Default,,0,0,0,,可是他一直不回来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.42,0:00:10.88,Default,,0,0,0,,樱都快气炸了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.88,0:00:11.97,Default,,0,0,0,,结果只有我们几个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.00,0:00:13.05,Default,,0,0,0,,就开始了再出发演唱会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.05,0:00:14.76,Default,,0,0,0,,当我们深陷在上次失败的阴影中时
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.76,0:00:16.03,Default,,0,0,0,,终于回来了的长发太郎先生
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.04,0:00:17.07,Default,,0,0,0,,被痛扁了一顿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.07,0:00:19.15,Default,,0,0,0,,看到他那样我们总算找回感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.15,0:00:20.84,Default,,0,0,0,,想办法让演唱会顺利落幕了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.84,0:00:22.81,Default,,0,0,0,,我们的卷土重来之路由此开始
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.81,0:00:24.10,Default,,0,0,0,,在佐贺逝去的七条生命
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.13,0:00:25.78,Default,,0,0,0,,带着丧尸的身体重新复活
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.78,0:00:27.49,Default,,0,0,0,,听从无理的要求唱歌跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.49,0:00:29.44,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀不做还有谁能办到呢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.58,0:00:40.81,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么了  樱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.82,0:00:43.70,Default,,0,0,0,,一想到我们真的又能
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.72,0:00:45.05,Default,,0,0,0,,开始进行偶像活动了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.05,0:00:46.73,Default,,0,0,0,,我就觉得有一点紧张
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.73,0:00:47.92,Default,,0,0,0,,这样很好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.92,0:00:49.41,Default,,0,0,0,,虽然早点习惯也很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.41,0:00:51.93,Default,,0,0,0,,但平常如果没有适度的紧张感也不好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.51,0:00:54.27,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲在做什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.18,0:00:59.62,Default,,0,0,0,,唱歌跳舞不是需要力量吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.63,0:01:01.85,Default,,0,0,0,,我们可是要称霸全国的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.18,0:01:04.67,Default,,0,0,0,,丧尸锻炼肌肉有意义吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.68,0:01:05.77,Default,,0,0,0,,这还用说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.77,0:01:07.95,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺湿布那么有效
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.95,0:01:08.92,Default,,0,0,0,,稍微锻炼一下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.95,0:01:10.08,Default,,0,0,0,,马上就会变壮了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.22,0:01:16.88,Default,,0,0,0,,再一次
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.88,0:01:20.60,Default,,0,0,0,,咲在不知不觉中就影响其他人了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.85,0:01:23.61,Default,,0,0,0,,大家都被她的热情感染了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.77,0:02:59.39,Default,,0,0,0,,大家早安  发生事件了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.60,0:03:02.66,Default,,0,0,0,,在全日本为新年号令和
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.69,0:03:04.00,Default,,0,0,0,,闹得沸沸扬扬之际
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.01,0:03:06.64,Default,,0,0,0,,传出了法兰秀秀将继续活动
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.65,0:03:08.67,Default,,0,0,0,,这项让佐贺的极少数人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.70,0:03:09.63,Default,,0,0,0,,振奋不已的新闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.63,0:03:10.60,Default,,0,0,0,,开始突击访问
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.60,0:03:11.48,Default,,0,0,0,,4号小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.48,0:03:13.21,Default,,0,0,0,,各位要继续进行活动了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.21,0:03:14.11,Default,,0,0,0,,请谈谈你的展望
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.71,0:03:16.57,Default,,0,0,0,,总之我们得想办法弥补
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.59,0:03:18.91,Default,,0,0,0,,停止活动的这个月耽误掉的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.31,0:03:21.28,Default,,0,0,0,,3号小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.29,0:03:22.53,Default,,0,0,0,,为了弥补耽误掉的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.53,0:03:24.02,Default,,0,0,0,,你们想进行什么活动呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.63,0:03:28.52,Default,,0,0,0,,除了积极进行基本的工作外
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.52,0:03:30.96,Default,,0,0,0,,也应该挑战其他的新事物才行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.18,0:03:33.95,Default,,0,0,0,,1号小姐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.95,0:03:35.93,Default,,0,0,0,,请举例一下是哪些新事物
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.62,0:03:38.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.87,0:03:40.03,Default,,0,0,0,,演戏之类的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.04,0:03:47.67,Default,,0,0,0,,上
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.21,0:03:49.41,Default,,0,0,0,,上台做蠢事时不要害羞
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.41,0:03:51.59,Default,,0,0,0,,是上电视啦
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.50,0:03:53.71,Default,,0,0,0,,你们现在必须做的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.71,0:03:55.07,Default,,0,0,0,,是向广大的年龄层
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.09,0:03:56.82,Default,,0,0,0,,宣传你们重新活动的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.82,0:03:59.22,Default,,0,0,0,,同时让大家留下冲击性的印象
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.22,0:04:00.01,Default,,0,0,0,,能办到这个的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.01,0:04:02.16,Default,,0,0,0,,说来说去也就只有上电视了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.16,0:04:03.65,Default,,0,0,0,,你这没路用的丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.73,0:04:09.78,Default,,0,0,0,,不要闹了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.78,0:04:11.93,Default,,0,0,0,,说起来明明全都是你害的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.65,0:04:15.43,Default,,0,0,0,,你刚才那样违反丧尸法哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.43,0:04:18.01,Default,,0,0,0,,你应该有事要先和我们说明吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.01,0:04:19.63,Default,,0,0,0,,好可怕好可怕好可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.63,0:04:21.03,Default,,0,0,0,,仗着自己是丧尸骚扰我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.04,0:04:22.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我要告你们哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.28,0:04:23.54,Default,,0,0,0,,丧尸骚扰丧尸骚扰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.54,0:04:24.33,Default,,0,0,0,,事情就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.33,0:04:25.52,Default,,0,0,0,,如果不想被告的话
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.52,0:04:27.21,Default,,0,0,0,,就快点去做我巽幸太郎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.23,0:04:29.14,Default,,0,0,0,,为你们争取到的大工作吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.14,0:04:30.22,Default,,0,0,0,,看过来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.39,0:04:35.08,Default,,0,0,0,,我要让你们上超有名的节目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.08,0:04:37.38,Default,,0,0,0,,到热门景点祐德稻荷神社进行采访
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.71,0:04:39.60,Default,,0,0,0,,大家都能上电视吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.60,0:04:42.41,Default,,0,0,0,,你的爸比说不定也会看到哦
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.41,0:04:45.20,Default,,0,0,0,,而且这次不是普通的采访
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.09,0:04:48.24,Default,,0,0,0,,和你们同样是受邀来宾的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.80,0:04:51.75,Default,,0,0,0,,那位白龙先生也会上节目
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.89,0:04:54.10,Default,,0,0,0,,白
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.13,0:04:56.48,Default,,0,0,0,,白龙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.87,0:04:59.35,Default,,0,0,0,,除了有进行音乐活动外
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.35,0:05:00.74,Default,,0,0,0,,他从1992年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.76,0:05:02.05,Default,,0,0,0,,就开始担任深夜广播节目
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.05,0:05:04.86,Default,,0,0,0,,"让佐贺之所以是佐贺"的节目主持人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.86,0:05:06.72,Default,,0,0,0,,获得全国年轻人支持
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.72,0:05:09.91,Default,,0,0,0,,来自佐贺的传说摇滚之星
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.91,0:05:11.80,Default,,0,0,0,,你在寻找的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.43,0:05:14.12,Default,,0,0,0,,永远都在佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.12,0:05:17.11,Default,,0,0,0,,真的是那个龙哥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.11,0:05:17.87,Default,,0,0,0,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.23,0:05:20.23,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥出道至今约三十年
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.23,0:05:21.61,Default,,0,0,0,,到现在仍在广播节目上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.64,0:05:23.91,Default,,0,0,0,,向佐贺的年轻人们持续传递信息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.54,0:05:27.12,Default,,0,0,0,,真的好厉害哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.12,0:05:29.98,Default,,0,0,0,,没想到佐贺有那么厉害的人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.98,0:05:31.63,Default,,0,0,0,,小心我宰了你哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.88,0:05:33.98,Default,,0,0,0,,你们通通听好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.39,0:05:35.75,Default,,0,0,0,,你们要好好宣传
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.78,0:05:36.63,Default,,0,0,0,,重新开始活动的消息
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.63,0:05:39.35,Default,,0,0,0,,然后和那些佐贺的传说们打好关系
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.35,0:05:40.95,Default,,0,0,0,,什么时候  什么时候去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.68,0:05:44.91,Default,,0,0,0,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.18,0:05:50.60,Default,,0,0,0,,从这边恰到好处地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.63,0:05:52.46,Default,,0,0,0,,走过门前商店街
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.46,0:05:54.21,Default,,0,0,0,,就会看见一座恰到好处的神社
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.61,0:05:55.54,Default,,0,0,0,,我们基本上
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.56,0:05:57.00,Default,,0,0,0,,都会提供恰到好处的大字报
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.00,0:05:58.38,Default,,0,0,0,,请恰到好处地多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.70,0:06:00.57,Default,,0,0,0,,请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.17,0:06:19.29,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么感觉和那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.66,0:06:32.79,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.55,0:06:35.37,Default,,0,0,0,,半路上从经岳吹下来的风
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.37,0:06:36.69,Default,,0,0,0,,将我给拦住了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.84,0:06:39.84,Default,,0,0,0,,真的是龙哥  绝对不会错
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.26,0:06:42.28,Default,,0,0,0,,有够土
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.57,0:06:46.27,Default,,0,0,0,,大家好
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.27,0:06:49.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我们是重新开始活动的法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.70,0:06:51.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.12,0:06:52.28,Default,,0,0,0,,和白龙先生
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.31,0:06:54.20,Default,,0,0,0,,一起来到了祐德稻荷神社
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.20,0:06:55.19,Default,,0,0,0,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.72,0:06:58.08,Default,,0,0,0,,请问您平时会常来这类型的地方吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.61,0:07:01.16,Default,,0,0,0,,如果你问我的话答案是YES
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.00,0:07:02.66,Default,,0,0,0,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.66,0:07:04.94,Default,,0,0,0,,如果你问佐贺的风的话就是
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.62,0:07:06.39,Default,,0,0,0,,YES
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.61,0:07:07.37,Default,,0,0,0,,YES
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.74,0:07:10.15,Default,,0,0,0,,樱  大字报出来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.17,0:07:13.80,Default,,0,0,0,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.36,0:07:15.69,Default,,0,0,0,,恰到好处
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.23,0:07:23.42,Default,,0,0,0,,这条商店街主打"一店逸品"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.42,0:07:26.07,Default,,0,0,0,,每家店都有自豪的优质商品
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.93,0:07:28.24,Default,,0,0,0,,我们到处绕一绕吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.10,0:07:37.46,Default,,0,0,0,,你在看什么啊  龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.92,0:07:38.47,Default,,0,0,0,,看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.87,0:07:42.17,Default,,0,0,0,,这些弹涂鱼被囚困在名为水槽的社会中
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.17,0:07:44.96,Default,,0,0,0,,就像是心中怀抱难以宣泄的愤怒的你们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.76,0:07:47.56,Default,,0,0,0,,真的耶
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.56,0:07:48.82,Default,,0,0,0,,它们就是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.45,0:07:51.64,Default,,0,0,0,,我想为它们打开通往自由的大门
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.37,0:07:53.25,Default,,0,0,0,,这些多少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.26,0:07:54.89,Default,,0,0,0,,那些是店里的宠物
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.89,0:07:57.02,Default,,0,0,0,,你就改买这个筷子架吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.02,0:07:58.32,Default,,0,0,0,,一个五百元
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.85,0:08:06.43,Default,,0,0,0,,自由啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.75,0:08:08.96,Default,,0,0,0,,这种感觉没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.35,0:08:11.09,Default,,0,0,0,,老实说气氛炒得挺热烈的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.09,0:08:12.12,Default,,0,0,0,,应该还算可以吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.90,0:08:14.91,Default,,0,0,0,,这座神社颜色好鲜艳哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.91,0:08:17.02,Default,,0,0,0,,看上去像玩具一样  好可爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.02,0:08:20.32,Default,,0,0,0,,和吉原的九郎稻荷截然不同呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.19,0:08:25.30,Default,,0,0,0,,小4  小4
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.30,0:08:26.35,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.35,0:08:28.51,Default,,0,0,0,,听说那边有供奉结缘之神哦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.51,0:08:29.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我们过去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.70,0:08:30.69,Default,,0,0,0,,结缘
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.17,0:08:32.43,Default,,0,0,0,,我没关系啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.82,0:08:40.76,Default,,0,0,0,,不晓得祂会不会听丧尸的心愿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.76,0:08:42.77,Default,,0,0,0,,神一定也会大吃一惊吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.49,0:08:49.64,Default,,0,0,0,,那么节目差不多要告一段落了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.64,0:08:50.27,Default,,0,0,0,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.82,0:08:53.86,Default,,0,0,0,,提到祐德稻荷的话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.89,0:08:55.32,Default,,0,0,0,,最大放异彩的确实是这间本殿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.80,0:08:59.04,Default,,0,0,0,,但要是被它的耀眼光芒夺去视线
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.04,0:09:00.34,Default,,0,0,0,,将会徬徨于黑暗中
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.34,0:09:03.33,Default,,0,0,0,,迟迟无法抵达前方的那个地点
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.23,0:09:06.39,Default,,0,0,0,,这是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.95,0:09:07.93,Default,,0,0,0,,现在这个时代
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.93,0:09:09.95,Default,,0,0,0,,真相早已被街道的灯火
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.97,0:09:11.20,Default,,0,0,0,,及喧闹的人群抹去了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.26,0:09:14.38,Default,,0,0,0,,如果有不惜匍匐前进
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.41,0:09:15.98,Default,,0,0,0,,也要追赶的觉悟我就带你去看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.37,0:09:21.83,Default,,0,0,0,,到奥之院去
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.26,0:09:23.84,Default,,0,0,0,,奥之院
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.21,0:09:25.31,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.31,0:09:27.11,Default,,0,0,0,,老实说奥之院走起来很累人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.11,0:09:28.24,Default,,0,0,0,,请让我们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.01,0:09:32.24,Default,,0,0,0,,我们现在已经自由了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.60,0:09:34.52,Default,,0,0,0,,老实说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.05,0:09:40.79,Default,,0,0,0,,完全看不到尽头呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.26,0:09:42.14,Default,,0,0,0,,如果还活着的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.17,0:09:43.73,Default,,0,0,0,,走起来一定会很累吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.30,0:09:46.34,Default,,0,0,0,,你等著  奥之院
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.24,0:09:57.29,Default,,0,0,0,,好棒哦
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.29,0:09:59.26,Default,,0,0,0,,从这里可以看见有明海呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.98,0:10:03.87,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.89,0:10:11.98,Default,,0,0,0,,掌握某些事物的过程
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.73,0:10:14.83,Default,,0,0,0,,总是会伴随着痛苦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.85,0:10:19.94,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.65,0:10:23.18,Default,,0,0,0,,老实说OK
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.19,0:10:24.32,Default,,0,0,0,,恰到好处
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.40,0:10:26.79,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀的那些女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.80,0:10:29.15,Default,,0,0,0,,相当努力和龙哥一起主持节目呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.58,0:10:31.19,Default,,0,0,0,,不管再怎么认真听
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.19,0:10:33.31,Default,,0,0,0,,都还是听不懂那个人在讲什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.15,0:10:36.13,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲  你不可以发火啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.48,0:10:38.44,Default,,0,0,0,,可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.69,0:10:44.31,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥说的话是灵魂的铁拳
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.62,0:10:45.69,Default,,0,0,0,,不能用听的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.69,0:10:47.21,Default,,0,0,0,,要用这里去感受才对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.30,0:10:51.12,Default,,0,0,0,,我过去一下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.12,0:10:51.99,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.97,0:10:53.66,Default,,0,0,0,,那个
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.52,0:10:58.91,Default,,0,0,0,,就是很高兴今天能见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.46,0:11:01.52,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥果然是最强的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.52,0:11:03.07,Default,,0,0,0,,非常谢谢您
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.92,0:11:07.10,Default,,0,0,0,,吹来了一阵不错的风啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.04,0:11:10.67,Default,,0,0,0,,我之前有阵子没办法听广播节目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.67,0:11:12.08,Default,,0,0,0,,但我一定还会再听的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.88,0:11:14.16,Default,,0,0,0,,随时欢迎你回来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.69,0:11:15.81,Default,,0,0,0,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.66,0:11:20.74,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我很快就会离开节目了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.29,0:11:24.06,Default,,0,0,0,,这也是时代的潮流啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.52,0:11:26.26,Default,,0,0,0,,请等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.78,0:11:28.17,Default,,0,0,0,,可是那个节目
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.58,0:11:30.81,Default,,0,0,0,,不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.81,0:11:32.63,Default,,0,0,0,,你在寻找的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.64,0:11:34.35,Default,,0,0,0,,永远都在佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.52,0:11:56.54,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲回来以后就一直那个样子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.86,0:11:59.28,Default,,0,0,0,,她是不是喜欢那个大叔啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.78,0:12:01.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你的意思是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.28,0:12:02.37,Default,,0,0,0,,她恋爱了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.37,0:12:03.24,Default,,0,0,0,,恋爱
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.24,0:12:05.55,Default,,0,0,0,,这也没什么好奇怪的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.55,0:12:08.79,Default,,0,0,0,,毕竟这种事是不分人类或丧尸的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.79,0:12:10.13,Default,,0,0,0,,不是丧尸的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.13,0:12:12.42,Default,,0,0,0,,重点是我们都是偶像啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.42,0:12:15.22,Default,,0,0,0,,偶像就不能喜欢上别人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.11,0:12:17.29,Default,,0,0,0,,应该不行吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.98,0:12:19.76,Default,,0,0,0,,如果这样能变得更耀眼的话
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.76,0:12:21.68,Default,,0,0,0,,莉莉觉得也没什么关系啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.69,0:12:22.90,Default,,0,0,0,,真的可以吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.80,0:12:25.82,Default,,0,0,0,,感觉无法完全否定这点呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.82,0:12:27.12,Default,,0,0,0,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.13,0:12:29.18,Default,,0,0,0,,当然要是真的有交往
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.18,0:12:30.85,Default,,0,0,0,,那就又另当别论了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.85,0:12:32.61,Default,,0,0,0,,不过从纯子那个年代
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.61,0:12:35.64,Default,,0,0,0,,好像就一直有偶像私底下谈恋爱哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.23,0:12:37.42,Default,,0,0,0,,是这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.91,0:12:39.67,Default,,0,0,0,,小爱也有喜欢的对象吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.19,0:12:41.95,Default,,0,0,0,,这种事我怎么可能说啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.95,0:12:44.48,Default,,0,0,0,,莉莉最喜欢全人类了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.48,0:12:47.32,Default,,0,0,0,,因为大家都最喜欢莉莉了呀
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.32,0:12:50.19,Default,,0,0,0,,我也最喜欢莉莉了哦
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.71,0:12:53.59,Default,,0,0,0,,总之现在先让咲一个人静一静吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.32,0:12:58.36,Default,,0,0,0,,广播笔名
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.36,0:13:00.92,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺警察脏兮兮哈利寄来的信
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.29,0:13:02.47,Default,,0,0,0,,又是你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.15,0:13:04.17,Default,,0,0,0,,"龙哥晚安"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.72,0:13:06.44,Default,,0,0,0,,"最近常去的小料理店"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.44,0:13:10.05,Default,,0,0,0,,"新雇了一位讲话充满古风的女性"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.57,0:13:12.34,Default,,0,0,0,,"从她看本官的眼光判断"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.34,0:13:14.56,Default,,0,0,0,,"她一定对本官有好感"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.76,0:13:16.77,Default,,0,0,0,,你想太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.77,0:13:17.75,Default,,0,0,0,,准备播歌了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.09,0:13:20.92,Default,,0,0,0,,白龙的"讨厌刮强风的日子吗 "
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.40,0:13:22.31,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.45,0:13:25.60,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉了  让你这么担心我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.88,0:13:30.94,Default,,0,0,0,,我第一次知道龙哥是中学时的事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.42,0:13:33.78,Default,,0,0,0,,那个时候的我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.78,0:13:36.90,Default,,0,0,0,,觉得全世界的所有人都是我的敌人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.94,0:13:39.77,Default,,0,0,0,,不管是老师还是周遭的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.77,0:13:42.56,Default,,0,0,0,,他们都想将不听话的我排除在外
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.82,0:13:47.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我拼了命地不断抵抗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.23,0:13:49.58,Default,,0,0,0,,为了不让自己就这么消失掉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.66,0:13:52.87,Default,,0,0,0,,就是在那个时候
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.63,0:14:04.38,Default,,0,0,0,,找不到自己的归宿
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.38,0:14:05.81,Default,,0,0,0,,对谁来说都是件难受的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.51,0:14:09.53,Default,,0,0,0,,但越是这种时候越不该遮蔽双眼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.53,0:14:10.75,Default,,0,0,0,,别摀住双耳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.35,0:14:13.36,Default,,0,0,0,,和你有着相同感受的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.37,0:14:14.71,Default,,0,0,0,,一定就在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.50,0:14:18.24,Default,,0,0,0,,从我现在对你讲话的这一刻起
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.24,0:14:19.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你就不再是孤单一人了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.86,0:14:23.35,Default,,0,0,0,,时间一久你八成也会将我给忘了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.92,0:14:24.99,Default,,0,0,0,,不过我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.99,0:14:26.59,Default,,0,0,0,,绝不会忘记和你的相遇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.59,0:14:29.31,Default,,0,0,0,,还有我们今天彼此交心的过往
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.15,0:14:33.30,Default,,0,0,0,,要是你感受到不安或是孤独时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.30,0:14:35.61,Default,,0,0,0,,随时欢迎你回到这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.85,0:14:38.31,Default,,0,0,0,,那是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.74,0:14:52.91,Default,,0,0,0,,和你有着相同感受的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.92,0:14:54.16,Default,,0,0,0,,一定就在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.51,0:14:59.50,Default,,0,0,0,,后来我就和丽子成为了拍档
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.51,0:15:01.53,Default,,0,0,0,,然后现在变成了丧尸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.53,0:15:04.07,Default,,0,0,0,,成为了樱和那些家伙的同伴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.10,0:15:06.70,Default,,0,0,0,,如果没有龙哥在的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.70,0:15:08.15,Default,,0,0,0,,当时的我一定会就那样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.00,0:15:10.81,Default,,0,0,0,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.60,0:15:13.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我还是没办法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.74,0:15:27.55,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺~佐贺~佐贺~
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.46,0:15:35.65,Default,,0,0,0,,自行车不能双载
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.35,0:15:57.51,Default,,0,0,0,,为了感谢大家热情的安可
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.97,0:15:59.18,Default,,0,0,0,,再来一首白龙的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.20,0:16:01.03,Default,,0,0,0,,"讨厌刮强风的日子吗 "
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.98,0:16:05.13,Default,,0,0,0,,打扰了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.32,0:16:13.41,Default,,0,0,0,,来了两只小猫
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.01,0:16:15.64,Default,,0,0,0,,看来应该不是误闯进来的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.46,0:16:19.83,Default,,0,0,0,,对了  听说法兰秀秀又开始活动了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.71,0:16:23.78,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊  官网首页也更新了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.46,0:16:26.01,Default,,0,0,0,,脏死了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.45,0:16:29.10,Default,,0,0,0,,OK
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.52,0:16:32.10,Default,,0,0,0,,看来今天会刮起一阵火热的狂风
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.58,0:16:34.08,Default,,0,0,0,,介绍两位突然造访的来宾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.58,0:16:37.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我是法兰秀秀2号  请多多指教
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.71,0:16:39.65,Default,,0,0,0,,我是法兰秀秀1号
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.66,0:16:41.44,Default,,0,0,0,,不好意思突然过来打扰
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.59,0:16:45.12,Default,,0,0,0,,所以你们过来有事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.49,0:16:48.46,Default,,0,0,0,,这个节目绝对不能就这样结束
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.46,0:16:51.61,Default,,0,0,0,,这个佐贺还有很多一直停滞不前的人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.61,0:16:52.37,Default,,0,0,0,,应该说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.37,0:16:54.34,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺本身就已经一直停滞不前了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.34,0:16:56.55,Default,,0,0,0,,要是龙哥不再主持广播节目的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.55,0:16:57.51,Default,,0,0,0,,那些家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.91,0:17:00.36,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺停滞不前的心灵又该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.13,0:17:03.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我现在之所以有办法当偶像
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.45,0:17:05.30,Default,,0,0,0,,就是因为有这个地方啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.89,0:17:06.70,Default,,0,0,0,,像我一样需要
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.72,0:17:09.03,Default,,0,0,0,,这个地方的人在这佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.03,0:17:11.91,Default,,0,0,0,,不  在全日本还有很多很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.91,0:17:13.50,Default,,0,0,0,,所以说拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.50,0:17:15.37,Default,,0,0,0,,请不要让广播节目结束
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.75,0:17:18.37,Default,,0,0,0,,请你继续当大家的归宿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.74,0:17:19.33,Default,,0,0,0,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.65,0:17:21.45,Default,,0,0,0,,不可或缺的不是我的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.47,0:17:22.77,Default,,0,0,0,,而是这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.36,0:17:26.07,Default,,0,0,0,,我不会平白无故消失的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.78,0:17:27.97,Default,,0,0,0,,我一直想将这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.99,0:17:29.91,Default,,0,0,0,,交给继承了热血之魂的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.27,0:17:34.16,Default,,0,0,0,,这家伙也已经垂头丧气好阵子了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.58,0:17:35.91,Default,,0,0,0,,就算你这样说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.44,0:17:38.01,Default,,0,0,0,,你在寻找的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.01,0:17:39.68,Default,,0,0,0,,永远都在佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.02,0:17:44.00,Default,,0,0,0,,这广播节目就交棒给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.84,0:17:49.62,Default,,0,0,0,,等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.62,0:17:51.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你们都来到我面前了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.86,0:17:53.55,Default,,0,0,0,,难道还需要其他理由吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.06,0:17:54.95,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.41,0:17:58.20,Default,,0,0,0,,你有着能吸引人们的热血之魂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.12,0:18:00.27,Default,,0,0,0,,不光只是法兰秀秀
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.07,0:18:03.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你要成为整个佐贺的队长
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.01,0:18:09.26,Default,,0,0,0,,法兰秀秀  队长2号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.26,0:18:10.79,Default,,0,0,0,,将会继承龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.81,0:18:12.82,Default,,0,0,0,,继续主持这个广播节目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.76,0:18:18.61,Default,,0,0,0,,他们怎么接二连三地擅自做起决定了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.61,0:18:19.74,Default,,0,0,0,,千万不要眨眼
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.74,0:18:22.17,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺在这一刻开始动起来了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.81,0:18:25.65,Default,,0,0,0,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.65,0:18:27.27,Default,,0,0,0,,佐贺就拜托你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.73,0:18:30.69,Default,,0,0,0,,请问
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.69,0:18:32.15,Default,,0,0,0,,你今后有什么打算呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.44,0:18:35.42,Default,,0,0,0,,从经岳吹下来的风
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.42,0:18:37.22,Default,,0,0,0,,在我背后推了我一把
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.92,0:18:40.01,Default,,0,0,0,,要我将佐贺的存在告诉世界
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.76,0:18:46.74,Default,,0,0,0,,龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.74,0:18:49.14,Default,,0,0,0,,我一直很喜欢龙哥
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.41,0:18:53.38,Default,,0,0,0,,混账东西
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.18,0:18:55.13,Default,,0,0,0,,现在你该传达
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.16,0:18:57.06,Default,,0,0,0,,热情之意的对象不是我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.22,0:19:00.40,Default,,0,0,0,,你要向那些停滞不前的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.88,0:19:03.15,Default,,0,0,0,,不  应该向这佐贺传达才对
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.82,0:19:05.45,Default,,0,0,0,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.54,0:19:11.04,Default,,0,0,0,,等你们将来再长大一点
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.04,0:19:13.30,Default,,0,0,0,,成为好女人之后我们再见吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.52,0:19:32.52,Default,,0,0,0,,真是个帅气的人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.70,0:19:34.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我想丽子她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.55,0:19:38.02,Default,,0,0,0,,或许就是遇见了那样的男人吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.51,0:19:40.52,Default,,0,0,0,,他还向我们说以后再见呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.72,0:19:43.77,Default,,0,0,0,,等再长大一点是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.30,0:19:45.46,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.56,0:19:48.65,Default,,0,0,0,,不管过多久我们都不会变成大人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.26,0:19:51.27,Default,,0,0,0,,更不可能成为好女人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.90,0:19:53.47,Default,,0,0,0,,因为我们是丧尸啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.74,0:19:58.24,Default,,0,0,0,,奇怪  怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.74,0:20:03.94,Default,,0,0,0,,小咲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.38,0:20:06.66,Default,,0,0,0,,怎么办怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.35,0:20:11.85,Default,,0,0,0,,我实在搞不懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.55,0:20:40.47,Default,,0,0,0,,为什么你也跟着哭出来了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.47,0:20:43.54,Default,,0,0,0,,可是小咲
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.52,0:20:45.72,Default,,0,0,0,,是我不好是我不好
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.72,0:20:47.37,Default,,0,0,0,,好了  你别哭了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.33,0:20:53.33,Default,,0,0,0,,你都快干掉了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.33,0:20:54.43,Default,,0,0,0,,不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.43,0:20:56.11,Default,,0,0,0,,糟糕糟糕糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.52,0:20:58.81,Default,,0,0,0,,樱  你真的要干掉了啦
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.53,0:21:02.89,Default,,0,0,0,,我们都听过广播了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.89,0:21:04.06,Default,,0,0,0,,今后就交给你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.06,0:21:06.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我们会支持你们重新进行活动的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.46,0:21:08.67,Default,,0,0,0,,我身为法兰秀秀的队长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.67,0:21:11.17,Default,,0,0,0,,一直燃烧灵魂站在舞台上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.69,0:21:12.48,Default,,0,0,0,,从今以后
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.48,0:21:14.50,Default,,0,0,0,,为了能成为佐贺的队长
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.50,0:21:17.74,Default,,0,0,0,,我将燃烧一亿万倍的灵魂站上舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.74,0:21:18.75,Default,,0,0,0,,如此一来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.75,0:21:20.61,Default,,0,0,0,,不管那些停滞不前的家伙人在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.61,0:21:22.39,Default,,0,0,0,,都能看见我热血的灵魂
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.00,0:21:23.88,Default,,0,0,0,,就像伊万里港的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.90,0:21:26.54,Default,,0,0,0,,浦之崎防波堤灯塔那样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.31,0:21:28.62,Default,,0,0,0,,那么各位请听
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:31.16,Default,,0,0,0,,"讨厌刮强风的日子吗 "
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.99,0:21:38.23,Default,,0,0,0,,通通给我拿出干劲来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.28,0:22:49.46,Default,,0,0,0,,从本周起由法兰秀秀接棒主持的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.47,0:22:52.36,Default,,0,0,0,,"让佐贺之所以是佐贺"要告一段落了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.85,0:22:55.09,Default,,0,0,0,,要是你感受到不安或是孤独时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.10,0:22:57.22,Default,,0,0,0,,随时欢迎你回到这个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.22,0:22:58.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我不管什么时候
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.34,0:23:01.91,Default,,0,0,0,,永远都会在你身边  不要担心
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.67,0:23:04.87,Default,,0,0,0,,敞开你的双眼和双耳
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.26,0:23:08.79,Default,,0,0,0,,举起你的灵魂铁拳吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.53,0:23:13.41,Default,,0,0,0,,不要忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.85,0:23:15.86,Default,,0,0,0,,你在寻找的答案
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.24,0:23:17.43,Default,,0,0,0,,永远都在佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.77,0:23:26.69,Default,,0,0,0,,我是咲
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.69,0:23:28.06,Default,,0,0,0,,对佐贺的热血之情
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.07,0:23:29.58,Default,,0,0,0,,我已经确实继承下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.58,0:23:31.10,Default,,0,0,0,,一起奋力一搏吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.11,0:23:32.10,Default,,0,0,0,,下一回的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.12,0:23:33.98,Default,,0,0,0,,《佐贺偶像是传奇·卷土重来》第三话
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.98,0:23:36.35,Default,,0,0,0,,爱与青春的木吉他·佐贺
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.35,0:23:37.62,Default,,0,0,0,,夜露死苦
